<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>vindication</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/vindication.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2005 03:03 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;[ajax] clee: i was wrong, you were right&lt;br /&gt;[clee] ajax: ?&lt;br /&gt;[ajax] clee: the Model M is a superior product&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>qotd 22/02</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/qotd_2202.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2005 00:01 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;[cliff] Hm. If I get a raise, I will buy a Powerbook. That will be like donating my raise to charity. (In the sense that the raise will not be reflected in my paychecks.)&lt;br /&gt;[cliff] And it will make the world a happier place. (Where &apos;the world&apos; is me.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>I&apos;m blogging this</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/blogging_this.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2005 01:53 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;davej and veebl are on my sofa. They&apos;re sitting in what currently acts as my bedroom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just thought I&apos;d blog that. ;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>subversion migration</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/KDE/subversion_migration.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2005 02:54 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the things I keep thinking about with KDE&apos;s much-vaunted CVS-&gt;SVN migration is... why don&apos;t we just leave the CVS server up as it is, and screw the whole &quot;import the entire history of our repository into SVN&quot; idea?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cvs2svn script is good. Don&apos;t get me wrong - it&apos;s pretty impressive. But we&apos;ve done some evil to our CVS repository - manually moved files, etc, and cvs2svn is not perfect; why don&apos;t we just leave the CVS server up and running read-only and import a snapshot (say, 3.4) into SVN without trying to drag all of the history along?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who want to pull absolutely 100% accurate checkouts of a given revision can do it with the old tools and we can evaluate subversion without having to deal with any possible issues brought up by weirdness caused by cvs2svn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I personally think this may be the smartest way to move forward, but I&apos;m sure that others have differing opinions. Care to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:clee@kde.org&quot;&gt;share them with me&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>lseek(fd, 0x5c, SEEK_SET)</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/redhat/lseek_0x5c.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2005 17:49 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Our Intel rep managed to secure me an 802.11a/b/g mini-PCI card for my ThinkPad. Direct from Intel. Totally sweet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Somehow managed to get the ThinkPad apart, and dropped in the new card, and connected the antennae, and turned it on, and was greeted rather rudely by two beeps and the infamous Error 1802.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was prepared for this though. I expected to spend the rest of the day hacking around IBM&apos;s evil authorized-miniPCI-card whitelist and being otherwise 1337 just like mjg59. But instead, I found the source for a neat little hack that resets part of the nvram to a magic value and disables the whitelist check.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All this means for those of you who don&apos;t speak Geek is that I overrode some IBM stupidity and made my hardware work the way it should. Which should have been much easier, but hey, this is Linux, and we like things like lseek(fd, 0x5c, SEEK_SET) just fine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Google Dinner beta</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/google_dinner_beta.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2005 09:32 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I spent most of this week at LinuxWorld in Boston (and the very beginning of the week at the XDevConf, which ajax took notes of) so my legs are killing me. But last night, Google sponsored this amazingly kick-ass dinner for a few dozen of us free software hacker types, and it was completely badass.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They had some issues with their food distribution algorithms though. Hopefully next year, if they roll out Google Dinner 2.0, they&apos;ll have that algorithm sorted out. (It took an inordinate amount of time to get our food since everyone had to wait in a huge line to get served - there&apos;s definitely room for optimization there, I think.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I talked Dave Jones into coming along and we had an awesome time. As soon as we walked in, we were accosted by Google folks who made us fill out some registration cards. One of the fields on the card said &quot;Desired position&quot; so I asked the woman (who had an amazingly kick-ass Google shirt, one with a female symbol on one of the &apos;o&apos;s in Google, but I digress) &quot;What does this &apos;desired position&apos; field mean?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;We want to know, if you were to work for us, what position would you want to have?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This stunned me. What an amazingly smart way of getting people interested. So davej and I filled in &quot;spaceman&quot; and &quot;Batman&quot; respectively. I mean, if Google is going to be hiring someone to be Batman, I certainly hope that they&apos;d consider me for the position, because I think I could do really well in that role.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Got to meet some cool people there, including &lt;a href=&quot;http://mako.yukidoke.org/copyrighteous/&quot;&gt;Mako&lt;/a&gt; who apparently wanted to meet me because he knew who I was. Finding out that other people &lt;i&gt;know who I am&lt;/i&gt; and want to meet me.... that&apos;s kinda freaky. I mean, granted, we&apos;re not talking about Havoc Pennington-style rockstar status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>xdevconf version 2.0</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/fdo/xdevconf_2.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2005 10:41 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Zack Rusin flew in and Adam Jackson drove up last night and both are crashing at my place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&apos;re at the X Developers&apos; Conference in Cambridge. ajax is taking notes, so I&apos;ll link to them once he uploads them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anyway. Back to the discussion about freedesktop and current level of desuckification.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>