<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>the past year</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/the_past_year.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2004 21:30 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I was reading &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.livejournal.com/~microtheist/&quot;&gt;Cliff&apos;s LiveJournal&lt;/a&gt; and I started thinking about my own life, especially the past year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overall, I have to admit that I&apos;m surprised at where I am today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I mean, a year ago... well, without going into &lt;b&gt;too&lt;/b&gt; many details, I don&apos;t think it&apos;s really an overstatement to say that October 2003 was by far the worst month of my life. (So far, anyway.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In short - I got laid off from my previous job; Mickey had sex with another guy while we were &quot;on a break;&quot; and I got into a car accident.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All in the space of about three weeks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This October is looking to be a lot better; I&apos;m working at Red Hat, and they absolutely kick ass. I&apos;ve still got the Tercel, and that car is awesome to drive. (The manual transmission continues to make me surprisingly giddy.) I&apos;m living in my own apartment, and the weather is getting cold enough that I can see my own breath. I finally managed to get the fuck out of Arizona, where it hit a hundred degrees last week. I&apos;m still single, and I continue to have the amazing luck of The Nice Guy, but I&apos;m used to that, so it&apos;s not really surprising. Being single is both better and worse; my relationship with Mickey was so fucked up that it was worse than being alone, overall, but I hate being alone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still, taking everything into consideration... I think I&apos;m doing a hell of a lot better where I am now. And it&apos;s good to know that - no matter how bad this month might be - it&apos;s going to be awfully hard for it to be worse than the same time last year.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>