<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>#if 0</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/fdo/if_0.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2005 01:21 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;There is a lot of really useless code sitting in Xorg today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was playing with a CVS checkout and noticed a large chunk of one of the source files was commented out with #if 0; so, this piqued my curiosity and I decided to figure out how many blocks of code are commented out with #if 0 in the server, driver, and lib trees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The current count, in CVS HEAD, as of about five minutes ago:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th&gt;module&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;blocks of #if 0 code&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;libs&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;56&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;server&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;408&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;drivers&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;648&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All combined, that&apos;s 1112 blocks of code completely disabled at compile time just sitting there in the tree.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Haven&apos;t bothered checking any of the other modules; I&apos;m sure there&apos;s more in apps but I don&apos;t really think it matters for docs or fonts. Still. That&apos;s a lot of useless crap.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>you know what to do</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/you_know_what_to_do.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2005 22:32 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;So, &lt;a href=&quot;http://livejournal.com/~ajaxxx/&quot;&gt;ajax&lt;/a&gt; and I are hanging out the other night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He heads to the fridge to grab a Coke, and comes back with a serious expression on his face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[ajax] Well, we have a couple of options.&lt;br /&gt;[clee] What?&lt;br /&gt;[ajax] There&apos;s only one Coke left. So, we can-&lt;br /&gt;[clee] Fight. To the death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good times. (Obviously, I won, since I&apos;m here to blog about it.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>tungsten e2</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/tungsten_e2.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2005 18:40 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;My Palm arrived yesterday, finally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ve been playing with it, and it seems to be a really cool device, barring a few issues. It feels very solid, and I like that. What I dislike is the software.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don&apos;t get me wrong - I love PalmOS, but PalmOS 5 is trying to do things it&apos;s just not capable of and Graffiti 2 makes me want to throw my shiny new toy into a wall. For example, the hack that the PalmOS guys are using for showing focus selection? It breaks with at least half of the color themes that they ship on the device, because it doesn&apos;t draw the halo properly on the buttons. And the fact that I can&apos;t create my *own* color theme annoys me, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I &lt;b&gt;need&lt;/b&gt; to figure out some way to get Graffiti 1 working on this thing. I&apos;m using a demo version of TealScript for now but it&apos;s a little on the slow side and I don&apos;t really like the idea of paying $30 for it, especially since it&apos;s *not* a faithful reproduction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sync works great over Bluetooth to my Mac mini, which is pleasing. The pilot-xfer command-line utilities on Linux seem to work very well too, which is good; I haven&apos;t tried any other utilities yet, but I will soon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>coincidence?</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/coincidence.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2005 02:59 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;ajax arrived a few minutes ago, and my inbox just hit 666 messages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;hmmm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>palm rant</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/palm_rant.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2005 20:35 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I blogged last month about switching my phone to Vonage, which has gone swimmingly well. I&apos;m really happy with Vonage, in that I haven&apos;t had to deal with them at all because their product just works (which is so rare in our industry that it&apos;s scary, and I&apos;m sad that I even find it noticeable that I&apos;m commenting on it), and also in that the features they provide seem to work really well. Being able to check my voicemail from the web is totally badass.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That said, since I no longer have a cell phone to keep my address book on, I decided to pick up a Palm once more. After checking out a few models and consulting with coworkers, I decided to pick up the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.palm.com/us/products/handhelds/tungsten-e2/&quot;&gt;Tungsten E2&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I put my order in on Tuesday, December 6th, and I made sure to select &apos;Overnight shipping&apos; because I&apos;m an impatient bastard and I want it &lt;b&gt;now&lt;/b&gt;. I would&apos;ve gone into a store to buy it, but it came with a free 128MB MMC flash card when I bought it online from Palm, and like a sucker, I decided to go for the freebie.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(I also noticed, just after submitting my order, that Amazon was selling the same exact handheld, sans the 128MB flash card, for $150. D&apos;oh.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just got a mail from Palm, &lt;b&gt;today&lt;/b&gt;, informing me that my order has been shipped.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I won&apos;t have it until Monday; even if UPS does deliver it tomorrow, I had it scheduled for an office delivery since I expected to be at work, and I&apos;m not planning on going in to the office tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other words, by the time I get it, it will have been almost a week since I placed the order. With &quot;Overnight&quot; shipping.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>vonage review</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/vonage.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 10 Nov 2005 02:58 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I decided that I was sick of paying too much money for my cell phone and so I&apos;ve initiated a transfer of my cell phone number from Sprint/Nextel to Vonage.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Vonage assigned me a temporary number in the meanwhile, which is cool, and I&apos;ve been playing with the service.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have to say that I&apos;m &lt;b&gt;really&lt;/b&gt; pleased with it so far.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Installation was literally a snap - I unpacked the router they sent me (the Linksys RTP300), plugged in the power, and scratched my head over what I should do next. I figured that I&apos;d probably have to do some port forwarding magic or something if I wanted it to work from behind the router, so I punted on that and went to Target to pick up a handset since I haven&apos;t ever owned a &quot;real&quot; phone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bought a $9 handset at Target, a GE &quot;Slimline&quot; thing that has call waiting, caller ID, three-way calling, and other things that are insane for a $9 phone. Anyway. I brought it back home, plugged it (and the ethernet cable) into my RTP300, and then mentally prepared myself for the frustration of having to do magic to get my main router to let the new toy do its thing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was a little disappointed, actually.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It just worked. No port forwarding, no iptables hackery, no headaches, no frustration - the lights flickered in a few weird patterns for a minute or so, and then I picked up the handset and I got a dial tone. I dialed my phone number and it asked me to log in to my voicemail.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Consider me impressed. Not to mention that the web-based UI for managing the Vonage account is really really sweet - I have it set to send me email when I get a new voicemail, and you can check your voicemails from the web (they show up as WAV files), plus it&apos;s dead simple to set up call forwarding and configure the different timeouts for voicemail/call forwarding/etc.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, I don&apos;t know about the other routers - I&apos;ve read lots of nightmare story reports from people using other hardware and things - or other phones or other VoIP providers, but so far I&apos;m pretty damned impressed with Vonage. Oh, and for $25/month, I get unlimited calls to anywhere in North America, including Canada, and their international rates are pretty good, too. I called &lt;a href=&quot;http://fooishbar.org/&quot;&gt;daniels&lt;/a&gt; up the other day and the conversation - which lasted for almost an hour - cost less than a combo meal at Burger King.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Pretty sure the future is made out of &lt;b&gt;awesome&lt;/b&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>qotd</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/qotd_110305.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2005 12:46 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;[ajax] alanc: oh, you mean like any sensible system would do&lt;br /&gt;[alanc] since when has sensibility had anything to do with how X is built?&lt;br /&gt;[ajax] touch&amp;eacute;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>qotd</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/qotd_102105.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 21 Oct 2005 11:40 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;[kfoltman] is there any way to &quot;record&quot; a group of drawing operations into a sort of metafile, then render that metafile on a printer &quot;drawing surface&quot;?&lt;br /&gt;[TD] kfoltman: yeah. it&apos;s called a PDF file ;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>planet update</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/KDE/planet_update.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 16 Oct 2005 00:03 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;For those of you who are syndicated on Planet KDE and also care about your bandwidth: Please pay attention to this message.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By default, Planet KDE will now show any images that you include in your blog. If you do not wish for images from your blog to show up on the Planet (which I can understand, since we do use up quite a bit of bandwidth), now you just have to do:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&amp;lt;img class=&quot;hidefromplanet&quot; src=&quot;foo.png&quot; /&amp;gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The old class=&quot;showonplanet&quot; is still around, but it&apos;s irrelevant now and may be removed in the future.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>qotd</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/qotd_101005.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2005 00:19 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;[@ajax] i have found the greatest flash game ever&lt;br /&gt;[@ajax] &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.ebaumsworld.com/kittycannon.html&quot;&gt;http://www.ebaumsworld.com/kittycannon.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;br /&gt;[@daniels] 595ft&lt;br /&gt;[@daniels] hm, 928ft&lt;br /&gt;[@ajax] 1144ft is my record so far&lt;br /&gt;[@daniels] now 1022&lt;br /&gt;[@ajax] i&apos;m pretty sure that if launching kittens out of cannons is wrong i don&apos;t want to be right&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>dogtail unleashed</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/dogtail_unleashed.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 07 Oct 2005 12:31 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Today is a pretty cool day for me because a project I&apos;ve been working on at work is finally released.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://people.redhat.com/zcerza/dogtail/&quot;&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;rapemewithachainsawthanks&quot; src=&quot;http://people.redhat.com/zcerza/dogtail/images/dogtail01.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;Dogtail!&quot; /&gt;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;dogtail is a framework written in Python which makes it easy to write scripts to automate graphical applications. It uses AT-SPI which means that (for now) it doesn&apos;t work with KDE, but I fought the good fight to make sure that it has no GNOME dependencies so that hopefully there will be a chance of KDE adopting it in the future. Now that we&apos;ve finally gotten the release out the door, I plan to track KDE svn and write scripts for KDE4 apps. Ideally, we&apos;ll have KDE4 support before KDE4 is actually released.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(I know that there&apos;s a tool from &lt;a href=&quot;http://wwww.klaralvdalens-datakonsult.se/&quot;&gt;KDAB&lt;/a&gt; which allows one to automate KDE apps, but it&apos;s not Open Source and it only works with KDE; dogtail supports anything that we can see through AT-SPI, which includes OpenOffice.org and Mozilla-based applications as well as, hopefully, KDE4.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>NetworkManager and KDE</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/KDE/networkmanager_and_kde.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2005 17:14 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.kdedevelopers.org/node/1465&quot;&gt;Fab&lt;/a&gt;: NetworkManager actually has a pretty well-designed separation between the front-end and the back-end; the only problem stalling us from being able to do cool things with it right now is that we have no working DBUS bindings for KDE3 (so nobody can easily write a Kicker applet to interface with NetworkManager to use on their desktop &lt;b&gt;today&lt;/b&gt;), and KDE4 doesn&apos;t actually have anything usable at this point, whatsoever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I brought this up at aKademy - aseigo and I were basically ready to go ahead with it but we got sidetracked with window icon previews in the window list on the desktop pager hover tooltip. (Try saying that five times fast.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In theory, somebody could write the applet using the DBUS API from C, but the current Qt bindings in the DBUS tree are pretty much worthless, so it&apos;s not going to be pretty either way.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>would you put your brain in a robot body?</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/robot_body.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 11 Sep 2005 05:49 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://wadejolson.blogspot.com/2005/09/where-in-world-is-carmen-sandiego.html&quot;&gt;Wade&lt;/a&gt;: No, I don&apos;t have a robot answering my email. My robots are busy preparing for the ... I mean, uh, what robots? I don&apos;t have any robots.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I do have three totally awesome computers now, though (not including my work laptop). The first one is my Mac mini, which rules, but it&apos;s not the focus of this entry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Over the past week or so, I&apos;d run into some really odd stability issues with my AMD64 box. I decided to go to CompUSA and pick up a new motherboard, since the last issue I had with an AMD64 machine was also the mobo. Bring the new mobo back home. Remove the old one, move parts over to new one, hook up power connectors, flip the switch, and ... nothing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The damned thing didn&apos;t even POST.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Somewhat frustrated, I decided to work on assembling my other new system. I&apos;ve had a spare CPU, some extra RAM, and a slew of video cards laying around for a while now, so the only thing I really needed to pick up was a new case and a motherboard for this box. It&apos;s an &quot;old&quot; AthlonXP 1700+ - I figure it&apos;s probably worth me keeping a system around that can do AGP and run fast enough to prevent me from throwing it out the window.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The assembly on my new system went pretty well, until the part where I attempted to attach the power cable. The power supply I was using was a 24-pin, designed for the power requirements of the newer AMD64 systems. Normally, it wouldn&apos;t be too hard to plug in a 24-pin cable into the 20-pin socket on the motherboard, except that the mobo I picked up happens to have the IDE pins right next to the ATX pins.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And there was much frustration.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was about to give up, but for some reason I decided to read the manual for the power supply in the new case that showed up, and if you look at page 3 in &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.antec.com/pdf/manuals/SmartPower2_En.pdf&quot;&gt;the manual&lt;/a&gt;, you should see the picture that made my night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The other power supply can break off the extra four pins so that I can use it on the motherboard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I returned to CompUSA and got a replacement for the busted motherboard, and brought it home and set it up, and this one actually works, so now I&apos;ve got both systems up and running beautifully.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My only issue now is that I need a DVI/USB KVM.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>thanks, Antonio</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/KDE/thanks.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Sep 2005 01:06 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Everybody else has been saying this on mailing-lists and whatnot, but I figured that it deserved saying on the Planet, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Antonio, aKademy 2005 rocked hardcore thanks to you and the LiMa guys. You guys kick ass. I didn&apos;t think it&apos;d be possible to top Kastle, but you guys did it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To next year! Helio, you ready for aKademy in Brazil? ;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>pronunciation is important</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/pronunciation.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 27 Aug 2005 04:13 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I finally got to meet a few people I hadn&apos;t met before, including aseigo. He&apos;s taller than I expected, at least. According to him, I don&apos;t look anything like what he thought I&apos;d look like, but I sound &lt;b&gt;exactly&lt;/b&gt; the way he thought I would. Along with Thomas Zander and Rainer Endres (and someone else whose name I can&apos;t remember) we left at around 1AM to go find a bar. We asked a couple of locals where a good place to get a drink would be, and they gave us some directions and told us to look for the &apos;Marabu&apos; or something similar. After about thirty seconds of walking, aseigo was already calling it the &apos;caribou&apos; and I had to correct him. Once we arrived in the area that they said it would be at, there was a building with with a bright neon pink heart sign that said &apos;Marib&amp;eacute;.&apos;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At this point, before entering, we had a couple of theories. One that we figured was likely was that the locals had sent us to a gay bar, which would have amused us. Rainer didn&apos;t want to go in, but I ventured in with aseigo and Thomas and the kid whose name I can&apos;t remember; I saw a bar with alcohol behind it and a bartender, so I went back to the door and motioned to Rainer that it was ok, it was just a bar, and everything looked fine.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rainer took a step in and then decided that he was going to go to the restaurant next door instead; I hadn&apos;t eaten or had anything to drink since much earlier, so I decided to join Rainer instead of staying with the other guys. Rainer ordered a beer, and I got a soda. About fifteen minutes later, aseigo and crew came out to join us and they were laughing pretty hard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apparently, the Marib&amp;eacute; is actually a brothel.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think that even funnier than finding that out (which was pretty funny) was the fact that aseigo even &lt;b&gt;saw&lt;/b&gt; the sign by the stairs that said &apos;Services&apos; with a man and a woman on it, and he didn&apos;t get it until the woman told him that the price was 20 EUR.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Update&lt;/b&gt;: It&apos;s worth noting that the Marabu was actually right next door to the restaurant that Rainer and I decided to go to; aseigo just couldn&apos;t resist the pink neon heart sign.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>proxima</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/proxima.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 25 Aug 2005 20:31 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Spain is pretty damned cool.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Well, ok, more accurately, Spanish women are pretty damned cool. I&apos;m pretty sure I&apos;ve seen more cleavage since I landed in Madrid than I have since I moved to Boston.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The trip has been exciting so far. There were two legs on the flight over - the stopover in Frankfurt was pretty uneventful. I was surprised by the fact that Lufthansa provided metal utensils for the in-flight meals; it impressed me, but at the same time, I had a realization. I shouldn&apos;t be impressed by metal silverware; I should be disappointed by plastic silverware. And on the flight from Frankfurt to Madrid, I was depressed - I guess the metal silverware is only for the cross-Atlantic flights. Anyway, once I landed, I wasn&apos;t too worried about navigating the Frankfurt airport; I&apos;ve been there before (the last time I came to a KDE conference, actually) and in general, I find airports to be reasonably simple to navigate, even if you don&apos;t speak the language.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The airport in Madrid was also pretty easy; figuring out how to get on the metro was not too hard, but it took a bit more walking than I expected it would. Once I was on the subway, I figured out pretty quickly that &apos;proxima&apos; is Spanish for &apos;next&apos; and I was set. The route that I had planned out actually worked exactly as I hoped it would. I got off the metro at the right stop for the train station and almost bought a ticket for the right train on the wrong day. Once I made it to the train, I figured I was pretty close to safe.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The train arrived exactly when expected, and there were lots of taxis outside of the train station waiting for us, which was good. The taxi driver I rode with didn&apos;t speak much English and had no idea where the place I wanted to go happened to be; he got directions from the central office, though, and somehow I managed to find the student residence where most of us are staying.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That&apos;s the last of this entry - there&apos;s more to follow, I promise.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>akademy 2005</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/akademy_2005.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 24 Aug 2005 05:27 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Tomorrow is going to be &lt;b&gt;interesting&lt;/b&gt;, I think.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&apos;m landing in an airport I&apos;ve never been to, in a country where I don&apos;t speak the native language, and I have to make it from the airport to the train station (which is not attached to the airport, but is at least two subway stops away). Once the train arrives at the destination, I still have to make it from the train station to the place I&apos;m actually staying, which is of course not exactly close by.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since I&apos;ll be in Spain and my phone won&apos;t work there, the best way to contact me is either IM or email; I won&apos;t be getting any voicemails until September 3 at the earliest.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>you exactly told me it was a magical goodies creator</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/magical_goodies_creator.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 Aug 2005 12:12 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Adam: I have a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.kdedevelopers.org/node/1320&quot;&gt;tax-free holiday&lt;/a&gt; every day of the week; it&apos;s called &quot;Living in New Hampshire.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(There&apos;s no sales tax in this state, for the readers out there who are confused.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Work on the tdfx EXA support is still ongoing; I have the framebuffer addresses properly set up now, but my blit and solid fill routines are completely hosed. At least I have an idea of how things are *supposed* to work now.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>way to go, sparks, you broke the monitor &lt;i&gt;and&lt;/i&gt; you&apos;re dead</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/way_to_go.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 Aug 2005 13:33 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Lots of things going on lately.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;First off, most recently, I started hacking on &lt;a href=&quot;http://c133.org/tmp/tdfx-exa.patch&quot;&gt;EXA support for the tdfx driver&lt;/a&gt; - it doesn&apos;t do much yet, except for display things wrong and crash, but hopefully I&apos;m not too far from it working properly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Second, I finally coerced a graphic designer friend of mine into coming up with a new layout for my site. It&apos;s not live yet, because I&apos;m not quite happy with it, but it&apos;s pretty close to ready (I think) - &lt;a href=&quot;http://c133.org/c133/&quot;&gt;take a look&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:clee@c133.org&quot;&gt;let me know&lt;/a&gt; what you think. (Yeah, I know, it&apos;s slow. It&apos;s using multiple layers of translucent PNGs, some of which are position: fixed. I prefer to think of it as &quot;an opportunity for KHTML optimization.&quot;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Third, I have been hacking on the &lt;a href=&quot;http://blogs.qtdeveloper.net/archives/2005/07/26/&quot;&gt;Qt4 BitTorrent client from Andreas&lt;/a&gt;, and it&apos;s really cool. There&apos;s a very small, slow memory leak in it, though, which I have to find and destroy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other than that, not too much going on. I&apos;m excited about aKademy - only a couple of weeks away!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>yes, carl</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/yes,_carl.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2005 02:05 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Stroking is hard. So hard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Every time I hear the word &apos;stroke&apos; from now on, I&apos;m going to hear keithp purr. That disturbs me to no end.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other news, the DDC at OLS has been a lot of fun. I&apos;m going to have to disagree with chouimat about a few things - namely, I think that Xgl is extremely sexy, and has a hell of a future, and while it&apos;s true that the vast majority of the talks here are GNOME-related or have a GNOME bias... it&apos;s because we are vastly outnumbered on this side of the pond, and you can count the number of KDE developers at this conference on one hand.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;George Staikos was here for a couple of hours, I&apos;ve been here for the DDC but not OLS, chouimat was here (but let&apos;s face it, you haven&apos;t been active in KDE lately, chouimat, and neither have I), and Alexander Dymo is here and gave a talk about KDevelop. We&apos;re not exactly taking over here. We need more of a presence at these shows, people. It&apos;s important.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>more cowbell</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/KDE/more_cowbell.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2005 04:46 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I may be abusing my &apos;tech/KDE&apos; category with this entry, but so be it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.more-cowbell.org/&quot;&gt;new tagging application called &apos;cowbell&apos;&lt;/a&gt; is out and it looks pretty boring. Reading through it I was mostly uninterested until I hit this part:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;It requires the Mono runtime, Gtk#, and TagLib to install and run.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Holy crap! GTK/GNOME apps using evil KDE technology! THE SKIES THEY ARE FALLING I TELL YOU.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seriously though, good on them. &lt;a href=&quot;http://developer.kde.org/~wheeler/taglib.html&quot;&gt;TagLib&lt;/a&gt; is good stuff, and I&apos;m glad to see that they&apos;re not reinventing the wheel. More projects need to use it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>kill all humans</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/kill_all_humans.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2005 04:06 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Some asshole thought it would be a good idea to string up yellow &quot;CAUTION&quot; tape and block one of the one-way roads leading to my apartment building inside of the complex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was not amused.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I stopped my car, pulled up the handbrake, flipped on the emergency lights, got out, and walked to one side of the tape. I ripped it off, and some guy screamed out &quot;HEY!!!&quot; I turned to his general direction and flipped him off, and walked across the street to the other side, where I pulled down the rest of the tape and tossed it into my car.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Got back into my car and parked in my parking lot without incident, throwing out the tape on my way in to my apartment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;God dammit, I hate people sometimes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>ikaruga</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/ikaruga.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2005 21:19 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Somehow, I just spent four hours playing Ikaruga.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.thebestpageintheuniverse.net/c.cgi?u=ikaruga&quot;&gt;They&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamespot.com/gamecube/action/ikaruga/review.html&quot;&gt;weren&apos;t&lt;/a&gt; &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.gamecritics.com/review/ikaruga/main.php&quot;&gt;kidding&lt;/a&gt;. This game is hard. Holy shit, this game is hard. I don&apos;t think I&apos;ve ever played a game where it took me four hours to get to the THIRD STAGE before. This game rules.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don&apos;t think I&apos;ll be sleeping this weekend.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(oh, and props to mpyne, who kicks *major* ass for dropping Ikaruga to me in the mail. The note he placed in the case reads &quot;Let me know how Level 3 is. I only ever made it to the boss of Level 2.&quot; Holy shit this game is hard.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>wireless future</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/wireless_future.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2005 03:08 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;(responding to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.chipx86.com/blog/archives/000100.html&quot;&gt;ChipX86&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;br /&gt;Dude. One word.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Batteries.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ok, to be slightly less cryptic: Wireless devices won&apos;t ever really replace their wired counterparts until they no longer require battery replacement to run. Batteries that recharge by gyroscopic motion? Ok, cool. Batteries that recharge by quantum phase induction? Hey, even if I just made it up, it sounds cool, and as long as it means that I don&apos;t have to put new batteries in when the current ones die, I&apos;m all over it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The main reason I don&apos;t have any wireless peripherals right now is the battery issue. I&apos;ve almost talked myself into getting one of the Logitech mice that recharges on the base station - that&apos;s pretty close to my ideal scenario. It takes the whole &quot;there&apos;s a battery inside&quot; detail and makes it completely irrelevant.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>build system notes</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/KDE/build_system_notes.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2005 22:34 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;We had a discussion in #kde-devel earlier about what KDE&apos;s requirements for a build system are. What are the current problems we have with autoconf/automake/libtool? What features do they provide that we really care about? How hard would it be to replace any/all of them with things that suck less?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I took notes of the discussion. They&apos;re below; I&apos;d like to get more feedback on this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(One of the first points that I&apos;m sure someone will make is &quot;auto* is cross-platform! We need to support KDE on platforms that aren&apos;t Linux!&quot; etc. Look, we realize this. However, auto* provides lots of problems for us on platforms we do care about, including MacOS X and Windows. (Ask RangerRick or js about them on IRC, or email them.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just because we&apos;re using auto* and friends doesn&apos;t mean that our code works; as a matter of fact, RangerRick noted that so far, all of his issues with the Mac port of the work-in-progress KDE4 have been build issues, and none of them have been code-related yet.  &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is clearly a problem and since KDE4 is an aggressive new major release, we should solve it in the KDE4 timeframe. We don&apos;t want to have to wait until KDE5 for a build system that doesn&apos;t suck, do we?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Without further ado, the notes from the discussion.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Must support:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;generating binaries (duh)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;generating shared libs (on all ELF platforms + MacOS X; Windows?)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;icon installation&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;uic, moc, KConfigXT, etc&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;GCC visibility&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;automatic dependency resolution&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;manual hints for dependency resolution&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;flex/bison&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;non-recursive (flat) builds&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;--enable-final&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;builddir != srcdir&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;simple to the point of being learnable within 5 minutes&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;kdeinit support (?)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;multiple build targets (libfoo, libbar, libbaz) in one file&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;--compile-slots, like in unsermake&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;pkg-config support&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;support rpath sanely&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;ability to link &amp; run uninstalled binaries&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;easily integrated into KDevelop&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;&apos;admin&apos; needs to be shipped in KDE instead of in src of each app (if we keep the &apos;admin&apos; dir, that is)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Would be nice, but not necessary:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;having a standard and distributed build system and test suite&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;li&gt;ability to build from svn:/trunk/KDE&lt;/li&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thoughts?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>cool interview</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/KDE/cool_interview.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2005 15:46 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strike&gt;Matt Harrison sent me a link to a &lt;a href=&quot;http://panela.blog-city.com/interview_with_kde_developer_ivor_hewitt.htm&quot;&gt;cool interview&lt;/a&gt; with Ivor Hewitt, one of the guys working on KHTML lately.&lt;/strike&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looks like the interview has been &lt;a href=&quot;http://panela.blog-city.com/removed_interview_with_ivor.htm&quot;&gt;taken down&lt;/a&gt;. Maybe it&apos;ll come back up soon.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ivor, do you have a blog? Because you should. Planet KDE could use some KHTML blogging love...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>wtf havoc</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/wtf_havoc.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 May 2005 14:43 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;[@hp] clee: hold me like you did by the lakes of naboo!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>I blame ajax</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/I_blame_ajax.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 May 2005 01:25 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt; * clee&lt;/b&gt; kicks ajax&lt;br /&gt;[clee] dammit, man. I really want a usable Expose feature. Like, yesterday would have been good.&lt;br /&gt;[ajax] oh yeah, totally my fault&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt; * clee&lt;/b&gt; blames you.&lt;br /&gt;[ajax] why yesterday?&lt;br /&gt;[clee] ajax: well, yesterday would have been good. today would have been acceptable. but if it gets here tomorrow, that&apos;s not soon enough.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt; * clee&lt;/b&gt; sighs&lt;br /&gt;[ajax] i was thinking maybe there was some event yesterday&lt;br /&gt;[clee] hahaha&lt;br /&gt;[clee] no.&lt;br /&gt;[ajax] like you were trying to show off X to some hottie in the coffee shop or something&lt;br /&gt;[clee] hahahaha&lt;br /&gt;[daniels] haha&lt;br /&gt;[clee] and she whips out a Mac and she&apos;s like &quot;Let&apos;s see your network-transparent windowing system do THIS!&quot; and hits F9?&lt;br /&gt;[ajax] but then she&apos;s all &quot;shit boy, five year old acceleration architectures ain&apos;t gonna get you any poon&quot;&lt;br /&gt;[clee] yeah, happens to me all the time&lt;br /&gt;[ajax] *smack*&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>vmware update</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/vmware_update.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2005 15:00 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Just thought I&apos;d post a quick update about my situation re: my computer at home, since I know you all care so much.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It turns out, after wiping my partition table and starting over from scratch and getting Linux back up (which took all of about ten minutes), Windows installed fine from the SATA DVD drive.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have no idea how this is possible - &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.windowsitpro.com/Article/ArticleID/41058/41058.html&quot;&gt;this page says&lt;/a&gt;, and I quote:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;Out of the box, no current Windows version, including Windows Server 2003, supports SATA drives.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My best guess is that the BIOS enables some sort of PATA emulation that Windows can use to find that drive. That&apos;s the only thing that makes sense.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And I was a little hard on VMware, to be honest. I mean, I was using a feature that &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.vmware.com/support/ws5/doc/disks_instraw_ws.html&quot;&gt;they specifically warn against most people using&lt;/a&gt;, while running 32-bit VMware on a 64-bit (unsupported variant of a) host OS. I&apos;m reminded of a quote here... &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;People who do stupid things with hazardous materials often die.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Granted, I didn&apos;t exactly die, but I think it somewhat applies.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>coolest thing I&apos;ve seen all week</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/coolest_thing_all_week.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2005 10:43 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.cnn.com/2005/TECH/04/29/spark.parajet/index.html&quot;&gt;Holy shit&lt;/a&gt;, this is awesome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seriously.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>unexpected results</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/unexpected_results.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2005 00:35 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Red Hat, my employer, has a site license for VMware. (Well, either a site license, or an assload of Workstation licenses, I&apos;m not really sure what the details are.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I decided &quot;Hey, why not play with the new release? You&apos;ve got new hardware. Maybe VMware will run acceptably fast on it!&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Man, what a fucking brilliant idea that was.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Backstory: I haven&apos;t booted Windows in a few months, not since Doom3 came out and wasn&apos;t available initially on Linux. However, I have some shiny new devices in the new box, including a SATA DVD burner, which so far doesn&apos;t seem to work with Linux very well. Ubuntu&apos;s kernel enables SATA ATAPI support, which Jeff Garzik tells me is a bad naughty thing of them to do since it&apos;s not ready yet. Which results in my ability to *see* the drive on /dev/scd0, if the planets align properly, but I can&apos;t actually use it for much.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This machine doesn&apos;t have a floppy drive, since I&apos;m a cheap bastard, and I happen to agree with Apple on this one. Fuck floppies. They should have died a long time ago. I also refuse to run Windows XP - I bought and paid for Windows 2000, a long time ago in a galaxy far far away, and it&apos;s the last release of Windows that I really plan on ever using. Windows 2000, being rather old, has some deficiencies, however. Like not having SATA support in the installer (unless you load a driver from a floppy, which I don&apos;t have).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think to myself, &quot;Hey! VMware! Raw disk support! It used to work pretty well, why not try doing an installation from a virtual machine into a physical disk? You can use the VM to download drivers, then create a new hardware profile, reboot into it, and maybe that&apos;ll work.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HAHAHAHAA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let&apos;s just say that this was probably the worst idea I&apos;ve had all night, even worse than eating that third slice of pizza. My partition table on /dev/hda now looks like this, thanks to VMware:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;pre&gt;Disk /dev/hda: 41.1 GB, 41174138880 bytes&lt;br /&gt;16 heads, 63 sectors/track, 79780 cylinders&lt;br /&gt;Units = cylinders of 1008 * 512 = 516096 bytes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This doesn&apos;t look like a partition table&lt;br /&gt;Probably you selected the wrong device.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;   Device Boot      Start         End      Blocks   Id  System&lt;br /&gt;/dev/hda1   ?      216399     1904881   850995205   72  Unknown&lt;br /&gt;Partition 1 does not end on cylinder boundary.&lt;br /&gt;/dev/hda2   ?      723265     1262922   271987362   74  Unknown&lt;br /&gt;Partition 2 does not end on cylinder boundary.&lt;br /&gt;/dev/hda3   ?      167316      167316           0   65  Novell Netware 386&lt;br /&gt;Partition 3 does not end on cylinder boundary.&lt;br /&gt;/dev/hda4         2671568     2671619       25817+   0  Empty&lt;br /&gt;Partition 4 does not end on cylinder boundary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Partition table entries are not in disk order&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&apos;m not even sure what to say about that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(For those of you wondering why I wanted to play with Windows in the first place - SATA DVD burner. I know that I can install Win2K drivers for the SATA chipset, and I know that the DVD burner will *probably* work there.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>joy!</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/joy.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2005 01:23 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;My new toys arrived today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That&apos;s one &lt;a href=&quot;http://c133.org/img/pc60.jpg&quot;&gt;Lian-Li PC-60&lt;/a&gt;, one Chaintech VNF4/Ultra motherboard, and one Athlon64 3000+ CPU.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This machine is officially fast enough to scare me. I can play Doom3 at my monitor&apos;s native resolution (1680x1050) and the frame rate doesn&apos;t drop below 60fps even with baddies on the screen.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The only other goodies I need to complete this box are a couple of 400G SATA drives. The Hitachi model is only $275 on NewEgg, which means that it&apos;s now possible to put over 1TB of storage into a box for under $1000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Holy shit life is good.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>new lease</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/new_lease.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2005 15:36 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Renewed my lease at my apartment for another year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I guess I&apos;m happy enough with Royal Crest. It&apos;s just that Cambridge is a lot cooler. If caillon and I had been able to get our act together earlier, things might have been different, but oh well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In any case, living at the same address for more than twelve months feels like some sort of a victory. Therefore, I win.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>as not seen on tv</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/not_seen_on_tv.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2005 04:46 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;showonplanet&quot; src=&quot;http://c133.org/img/clee-sp.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.planearium2.de/flash/sp-studio-e.html&quot;&gt;Heh&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>almost normal</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/almost_normal.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2005 02:56 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I&apos;m feeling much healthier. Maybe the title is a bit of a misnomer, since we all know that I&apos;m not anywhere close to &quot;normal,&quot; but my throat seems to be almost completely healed and it no longer hurts to breathe, eat, or swallow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By some assorted cleverness, I have managed to secure an upgrade to an Athlon 64 and a much nicer new case, for a net cost of about $20 to me. I&apos;m excited.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I need to pick a project to get back into KDE hacking with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not much else is new. Found a really awesome pizza place a few weeks ago, and have been eating there regularly. A $10 pizza lasts me two or three days, which is awesome. Saving money is good.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>ow</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/ow.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2005 13:53 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;strep throat sucks. I&apos;ve had this soreness in my throat since Friday last week, and it kept getting worse. Finally, on Sunday, I went to the doctor and found out &quot;Hey, you&apos;ve got strep!&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now I&apos;ve got penicillin and cough drops. Throat still hurts. Wish my white blood cells weren&apos;t such little bitches. They&apos;re supposed to *handle* this stuff for me, dammit.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>rant part deux</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/rant_part_deux.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2005 19:14 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Several people were kind enough to point out that this code:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;br /&gt;for i in xrange(foo):&lt;br /&gt;    print i&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br /&gt;actually wouldn&apos;t work. Thanks, I&apos;m an idiot. I should have had:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;br /&gt;for i in xrange(len(foo)):&lt;br /&gt;    print i&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next, yet another method of reversing/iterating backwards over a list has been suggested in multiple places, one which I didn&apos;t know about.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;br /&gt;foo = [&apos;one&apos;, &apos;two&apos;, &apos;three&apos;]&lt;br /&gt;bar = foo[::-1]&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The only thing I can possibly say to that is... but the ternary operator is too obscure? C&apos;mon, give me a break. This provides the ability to have tons of random line noise and make your code just as unreadable.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And, &lt;a href=&quot;http://blog.sethdot.org/index.cgi/223&quot;&gt;Seth&lt;/a&gt;: Since I couldn&apos;t catch you on IRC earlier, I&apos;ll just reply here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Multiple issues to respond to, so let me break it down.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ol&gt; &lt;li&gt;You seem to be confused as to what I was complaining about with &lt;code&gt;list.reverse()&lt;/code&gt;. It&apos;s not that I want a copy of the list, exactly, but I want the return value of &lt;code&gt;list.reverse()&lt;/code&gt; to be sane, which in my exceedingly humble opinion, it is nowhere near.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;I&apos;m not upset, mind you, just mildly annoyed, by the iteritems()/enumerate()/xrange() issue. And the reason that it&apos;s annoying to me is because it&apos;s inconsistent. Some of the iterator methods are global and some of them are not. Inconsistency is lame. End of topic.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Ternary operators seem to be quite the polarizing issue so I&apos;ll just leave my stance exactly where it is. I think they&apos;re useful, and I&apos;d like to have them, but obviously I can work around the language not having them...&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Especially since Python doesn&apos;t have sane scoping, either; the method-local and class-local scoping rules provide the opportunity for &lt;b&gt;way&lt;/b&gt; too many obscure and annoying bugs. I note that you didn&apos;t respond to my issue with scoping at all.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oh, also, a friend of mine has offered to send you a copy of the Smalltalk book, where he says that they solved the problem of doing lambdas and maps efficiently.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ll kindly ignore your not-so-subtle digs at my programming ability (or perceived lack thereof) and refuse to insult you for liking Python. Mind you, I still think it&apos;s a useful language, but I&apos;m just annoyed at the inconsistencies and some pet features (like ternary operators, or sane scoping) that I wish it had.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>python rant</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/python_rant.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2005 04:25 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;(This is a pretty geeky entry, so if you&apos;re not a geek, consider yourself warned.)&lt;br /&gt;I have a lot of little tiny annoyances with python, since I&apos;ve been using it for a while now to hack on some stuff. Here&apos;s a collection of the ones that are floating on top of my brain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;::sniff::&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;br /&gt;I miss my ternary operator.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In C, and C++, and Perl, and Ruby, and PHP, and pretty much any language that I&apos;ve ever written in (hell, I think even JavaScript supports this, though I could be wrong about that one since I haven&apos;t written any JavaScript code in years), you can use a very terse syntax for &lt;code&gt;if (foo) { return bar; } else { return baz; }&lt;/code&gt; using what is referred to as the ternary operator.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The shortened syntax is more like:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(foo ? bar : baz)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yeah, it&apos;s kinda weird. And yeah, if you don&apos;t understand it, it&apos;s not very intuitive. However, it makes for much shorter and clearer code (to those who grok ternary operators). Python doesn&apos;t support this. At all. There was a proposal to include it and it got smacked down, so that they could include such other genius ideas as &lt;code&gt;reversed()&lt;/code&gt; instead. Speaking of which...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;backwards&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Reversing an array is done like:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;br /&gt;foo = [&apos;one&apos;, &apos;two&apos;, &apos;three&apos;]&lt;br /&gt;foo.reverse()&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br /&gt;This does not return a reversed copy of the array, but it does reverse the array in-place and return &apos;None&apos; which is quite confusing. Especially if you&apos;re used to sensible languages which return a reversed copy. So this code doesn&apos;t work.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;br /&gt;foo = [&apos;one&apos;, &apos;two&apos;, &apos;three&apos;]&lt;br /&gt;for i in foo.reverse(): &lt;span color=&quot;#29416C&quot;&gt;# bzzzt, reverse() returns &apos;None&apos;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;	print i&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br /&gt;You &lt;b&gt;can&lt;/b&gt; iterate through an array with the &lt;code&gt;reversed()&lt;/code&gt; keyword, like:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;br /&gt;for i in reversed(foo):&lt;br /&gt;	print i&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;However&lt;/b&gt;, this is a python-2.4-specific feature, so it&apos;s useless if you care about older python releases. Also, it doesn&apos;t create a reversed array, just hands you a pointer to a reversed list iterator. So you can&apos;t do:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;br /&gt;foo = [&apos;one&apos;, &apos;two&apos;, &apos;three&apos;]&lt;br /&gt;bar = reversed(foo)&lt;br /&gt;print bar[0] &lt;span color=&quot;#29416C&quot;&gt;# &apos;three&apos;? how about a TypeError!&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because &lt;code&gt;bar&lt;/code&gt; is actually not a list, or array, or what-have-you, but it&apos;s a listreverseiterator object. Whatever the hell that&apos;s supposed to mean. What it translates into is basically &quot;Surprise! We hate you.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, you have to do:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;br /&gt;foo = [&apos;one&apos;, &apos;two&apos;, &apos;three&apos;]&lt;br /&gt;foo.reverse()&lt;br /&gt;for i in foo:&lt;br /&gt;	print i&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Which, granted, ok, isn&apos;t the end of the world, but it&apos;s pretty ugly and it doesn&apos;t work at &lt;b&gt;all&lt;/b&gt; the way I had expected it to, which to me is the sign of a language that sucks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For reference, the following code in ruby does work exactly how I expected it to. And because ruby and python share a decent amount of syntactical sugar, I keep on getting annoyed when things that I expect to be working in python simply aren&apos;t.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;br /&gt;foo = [&apos;a&apos;, &apos;b&apos;, &apos;c&apos;]&lt;br /&gt;p foo.reverse() &lt;span color=&quot;#29416c&quot;&gt;# prints out &quot;[&apos;c&apos;, &apos;b&apos;, &apos;a&apos;]&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;foo.reverse().each { |i|&lt;br /&gt;	print i&lt;br /&gt;}&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Ruby&apos;s list iterators are weird, sure. But actually, that&apos;s a good way to bring up my next complaint.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;iterators in general&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Why the hell do you have multiple types of list iterator methods in python? I shouldn&apos;t have to remember a different type of iterator method for every different type of container, nor should I have to remember whether it&apos;s a global iterator method or a per-container one. That&apos;s just annoying, and pointless.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, you have &lt;code&gt;foo = [&apos;a&apos;, &apos;b&apos;, &apos;c&apos;]&lt;/code&gt;, right.&lt;br /&gt;Now, to recap, you can traverse the list backwards (in 2.4, anyway) with:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;br /&gt;for i in reversed(foo):&lt;br /&gt;	print i&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can get the indexes of the members of the list with:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;br /&gt;for i in xrange(foo):&lt;br /&gt;	print i &lt;span color=&quot;#29416C&quot;&gt;# Prints out the index of each member&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;You can also do:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;br /&gt;for i, n in enumerate(foo):&lt;br /&gt;	print i, n &lt;span color=&quot;#29416C&quot;&gt;# Prints the index and the member&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Although I have no idea why you&apos;d want to. (You can always just do xrange(foo) and then &apos;foo[i]&apos; since they give you the same thing. But ternary operators would be too confusing.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But, if you have a dict instead of a list, all of a sudden...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;br /&gt;foo = { &apos;a&apos;:1, &apos;b&apos;:2, &apos;c&apos;:3 }&lt;br /&gt;for i, n in foo.iteritems():&lt;br /&gt;	print i, n&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using &lt;code&gt;enumerate()&lt;/code&gt; gives you the index of the &apos;a&apos;, &apos;b&apos;, and &apos;c&apos; keys. Also, note that &lt;code&gt;enumerate()&lt;/code&gt; is a global, like &lt;code&gt;reversed()&lt;/code&gt;, but &lt;code&gt;iteritems()&lt;/code&gt; is a member of the dict class type. This is the kind of inconsistency in a language that kills me.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;white space&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Surprisingly, I don&apos;t mind the whitespace thing. It just doesn&apos;t bother me that much. (Ok, so that&apos;s not really a complaint. Still, enough other people complain that I figured it was worth noting that it just doesn&apos;t irk me.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;h4&gt;scoping&lt;/h4&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Scoping is &lt;b&gt;weird&lt;/b&gt; in python. Let me explain.&lt;br /&gt;In regular languages, a variable declared inside of a block of code only lives until the end of that block; this is the &apos;scope&apos; of the variable. So if you have:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;br /&gt;if (condition) {&lt;br /&gt;	string foo = &quot;hahahaha&quot;;&lt;br /&gt;}&lt;br /&gt;print (foo); &lt;span color=&quot;#29416C&quot;&gt;/* Error! &apos;foo&apos; didn&apos;t make it past that last &apos;}&apos; */&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;br /&gt;(Yeah, that&apos;s not a real language, though I suppose it could be valid C or C++ or something. I don&apos;t care, it&apos;s just there to illustrate a point.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But in python, guess what?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;pre&gt;&lt;br /&gt;if condition:&lt;br /&gt;	foo = &quot;hahahaha&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;print foo &lt;span color=&quot;#29416C&quot;&gt;# This actually &lt;b&gt;*works*&lt;/b&gt; - wtf?&lt;/span&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are other issues that annoy me, but these are just the ones on top of my head. I&apos;ll write another rant if this one pisses off enough python devs.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>toys</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/toys.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 15 Apr 2005 01:16 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;The other day, I was on Dell&apos;s website. They had the 2005FPW for 25% off, and I thought to myself, &quot;Self, that&apos;s a damned good deal.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, I didn&apos;t have $561.75 free on any of my accounts, and the deal expired in a few days. Then I saw the &quot;Apply now&quot; link. &quot;Hmm, instant loan. Nah, you already have too much credit.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wait, though. If you apply for credit and you get rejected, at least in the US, you&apos;re automatically entitled to a free credit report. What the hell, why not? I can always use a free copy of my credit report.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;About three minutes later, the Dell website comes back with the result. &quot;Congratulations! You qualify for a $1500 line of credit.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Shit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Needless to say, now I have a sweet 20&quot; widescreen LCD. It&apos;s gorgeous. I liked it so much that I bragged to pretty much everyone that would listen. And I even convinced ajax to buy one, but he went and bought three instead. Crazy bastard.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&apos;d post pics, but I don&apos;t have a digital camera. Mostly because when I buy one, I want it to kick ass, and the ones that I want are still over $1000.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Note: All amounts in USD.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>wtf xda</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/fdo/wtf_xda.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 05 Apr 2005 22:59 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;[@ajax] so working on DRI for i128, i turned off XAA&lt;br /&gt;[@ajax] in the spirit of experimentation, i ran xcompmgr -a&lt;br /&gt;[@ajax] it feels _much_ faster now&lt;br /&gt;[@ajax] like, firefox doesn&apos;t tear when scrolling&lt;br /&gt;[@ajax] it&apos;s kinda weird&lt;br /&gt;[@daniels] hmm&lt;br /&gt;[@daniels] maybe we should rename it to XDA :P&lt;br /&gt;[@ajax] totally unaccelerated, but just fast enough to feel useful&lt;br /&gt;[@ajax] the only unpleasant part is switching desktops&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>gah</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/gah.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2005 00:35 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I hate caffeine deprivation headaches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(For those of you following from home, yes, I had successfully kicked my caffine habit but then I realized that not drinking it sucked. So I started drinking it again. And just now, I went a couple of days without - again - and all of a sudden I&apos;ve got the headaches. Fuck.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also, Smallville is still one of my favorite TV shows. I honestly can&apos;t decide if I like it more than Battlestar Galactica or not.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>congratulations, zack</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/KDE/congratulations_zack.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2005 17:07 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Major kudos to Zack Rusin for getting hired at Trolltech.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Not like it should be a surprise to anyone, since Zack kicks ass and Trolltech also kicks ass.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This bodes extremely well for KDE4. World domination!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>qotd</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/qotd_brandi.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2005 01:24 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;&quot;You are like, so much better than a bathroom stall.&quot;&lt;br /&gt;-Brandi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>spin spin</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/fdo/spin_spin.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2005 17:27 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.livejournal.com/users/spyderous/13259.html&quot;&gt;Donnie&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&quot;http://planetKDE.org/&quot;&gt;Planet KDE&lt;/a&gt;, and every ten minutes. I&apos;m thinking about changing it to update every fifteen, though. We&apos;re getting enough feeds that we&apos;re spending more time updating than idling.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>qotd</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/qotd_mar07.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2005 17:28 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;[mgalgoci] policy I&apos;d like to have set: &quot;When people ask for email aliases, the aliases are granted on the grounds that IS gets to decide what the alias is.&quot;&lt;br /&gt;[clee] mgalgoci: oh, oh! what&apos;s mine?&lt;br /&gt;[hp] clee: I think your native american name is he-who-hopes-to-get-laid-using-enterprise-groupware-solution&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>musings</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/musings.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2005 05:05 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s 5AM.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&apos;m blind, and it&apos;s dark. Music from Metal Gear Solid 3 floats through my apartment and yet I can still hear the drops of blood hitting the surface of the water as my nose drains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nosebleeds have been a pretty common occurrence for about as long as I can remember; I&apos;ve had them ever since I was a little kid. They&apos;ve started back up recently, after I had gone several months without having any. I&apos;m not sure exactly why but I think it might be somewhat related to drinking soda. (While I was caffeine-free for that six weeks or so, I didn&apos;t have a single nosebleed.) I&apos;ve recently started drinking the stuff again, since it&apos;s easier to drink it than not to, but I may have to rethink that choice in light of this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oh well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Speaking of Metal Gear Solid 3, I finally sat down and played through the rest of it. I had gotten farther along than I thought before I stopped playing it back in November, and the game is just amazing. I can&apos;t think of enough words to describe how much I enjoyed playing through this game.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>vindication</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/vindication.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2005 03:03 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;[ajax] clee: i was wrong, you were right&lt;br /&gt;[clee] ajax: ?&lt;br /&gt;[ajax] clee: the Model M is a superior product&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>qotd 22/02</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/qotd_2202.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2005 00:01 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;[cliff] Hm. If I get a raise, I will buy a Powerbook. That will be like donating my raise to charity. (In the sense that the raise will not be reflected in my paychecks.)&lt;br /&gt;[cliff] And it will make the world a happier place. (Where &apos;the world&apos; is me.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>I&apos;m blogging this</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/blogging_this.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2005 01:53 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;davej and veebl are on my sofa. They&apos;re sitting in what currently acts as my bedroom.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just thought I&apos;d blog that. ;)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>subversion migration</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/KDE/subversion_migration.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2005 02:54 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;One of the things I keep thinking about with KDE&apos;s much-vaunted CVS-&gt;SVN migration is... why don&apos;t we just leave the CVS server up as it is, and screw the whole &quot;import the entire history of our repository into SVN&quot; idea?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Think about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cvs2svn script is good. Don&apos;t get me wrong - it&apos;s pretty impressive. But we&apos;ve done some evil to our CVS repository - manually moved files, etc, and cvs2svn is not perfect; why don&apos;t we just leave the CVS server up and running read-only and import a snapshot (say, 3.4) into SVN without trying to drag all of the history along?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;People who want to pull absolutely 100% accurate checkouts of a given revision can do it with the old tools and we can evaluate subversion without having to deal with any possible issues brought up by weirdness caused by cvs2svn.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I personally think this may be the smartest way to move forward, but I&apos;m sure that others have differing opinions. Care to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:clee@kde.org&quot;&gt;share them with me&lt;/a&gt;?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>lseek(fd, 0x5c, SEEK_SET)</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/redhat/lseek_0x5c.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2005 17:49 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Our Intel rep managed to secure me an 802.11a/b/g mini-PCI card for my ThinkPad. Direct from Intel. Totally sweet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Somehow managed to get the ThinkPad apart, and dropped in the new card, and connected the antennae, and turned it on, and was greeted rather rudely by two beeps and the infamous Error 1802.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was prepared for this though. I expected to spend the rest of the day hacking around IBM&apos;s evil authorized-miniPCI-card whitelist and being otherwise 1337 just like mjg59. But instead, I found the source for a neat little hack that resets part of the nvram to a magic value and disables the whitelist check.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All this means for those of you who don&apos;t speak Geek is that I overrode some IBM stupidity and made my hardware work the way it should. Which should have been much easier, but hey, this is Linux, and we like things like lseek(fd, 0x5c, SEEK_SET) just fine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Google Dinner beta</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/google_dinner_beta.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2005 09:32 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I spent most of this week at LinuxWorld in Boston (and the very beginning of the week at the XDevConf, which ajax took notes of) so my legs are killing me. But last night, Google sponsored this amazingly kick-ass dinner for a few dozen of us free software hacker types, and it was completely badass.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They had some issues with their food distribution algorithms though. Hopefully next year, if they roll out Google Dinner 2.0, they&apos;ll have that algorithm sorted out. (It took an inordinate amount of time to get our food since everyone had to wait in a huge line to get served - there&apos;s definitely room for optimization there, I think.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I talked Dave Jones into coming along and we had an awesome time. As soon as we walked in, we were accosted by Google folks who made us fill out some registration cards. One of the fields on the card said &quot;Desired position&quot; so I asked the woman (who had an amazingly kick-ass Google shirt, one with a female symbol on one of the &apos;o&apos;s in Google, but I digress) &quot;What does this &apos;desired position&apos; field mean?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;We want to know, if you were to work for us, what position would you want to have?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This stunned me. What an amazingly smart way of getting people interested. So davej and I filled in &quot;spaceman&quot; and &quot;Batman&quot; respectively. I mean, if Google is going to be hiring someone to be Batman, I certainly hope that they&apos;d consider me for the position, because I think I could do really well in that role.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Got to meet some cool people there, including &lt;a href=&quot;http://mako.yukidoke.org/copyrighteous/&quot;&gt;Mako&lt;/a&gt; who apparently wanted to meet me because he knew who I was. Finding out that other people &lt;i&gt;know who I am&lt;/i&gt; and want to meet me.... that&apos;s kinda freaky. I mean, granted, we&apos;re not talking about Havoc Pennington-style rockstar status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>xdevconf version 2.0</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/fdo/xdevconf_2.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 12 Feb 2005 10:41 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Zack Rusin flew in and Adam Jackson drove up last night and both are crashing at my place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&apos;re at the X Developers&apos; Conference in Cambridge. ajax is taking notes, so I&apos;ll link to them once he uploads them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anyway. Back to the discussion about freedesktop and current level of desuckification.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>world of warcrack</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/world_of_warcrack.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2005 20:59 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I attempted to hunt down a copy of World of Warcraft a few weeks ago, in vain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My searches were fruitless. I went to several Wal-Marts, Targets, and Gamestops. All were completely devoid of World of Warcraft loving. This made me sad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I ended up going to go visit Tony (who I&apos;ll be dropping by to see again on the sixth for the Chinese New Year) and I crashed at his place after he, Rob, and I stayed up until way too late watching Battlestar Galactica at Rob&apos;s place. The following morning, we got up and I talked Tony into going to the Apple store. It wasn&apos;t that hard to convince him, actually. I just said &quot;We&apos;re going to the Apple Store,&quot; and he complied. Once there, I had the instant flash of realization that the wonderful bastards at Blizzard put the Mac and PC versions of their games on the same CDs. Those crazy fools. I searched for the gem and - lo and behold - there were FIVE copies of WoW. I picked mine up, made sure it wasn&apos;t some book or gift card (like Target had. For shame, Target! For shame.) and I carried it to the line at the register and bought it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The game is incredible. It&apos;s seriously just amazing. If only I had a decent video card, one that didn&apos;t overheat when I played it... And dealing with Windows is shitty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Which is why I&apos;ve bought a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.apple.com/macmini/&quot;&gt;dedicated World of Warcraft box&lt;/a&gt;. It hasn&apos;t arrived yet, which irks me. But it should be here &quot;on or before&quot; the seventeenth of February, according to Apple. Huzzah for that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That&apos;s about all that&apos;s new in the past few weeks. I&apos;ll attempt to blog more frequently - hey, I should dump my .plan on here sometime and see what people think - but it&apos;d probably be easier if I had my blogging app working again. Sounds like a fun project for tonight!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>the other british dave</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/the_other_british_dave.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2005 20:49 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Spent the entire weekend hanging out with Dave Jones, kernel slacker extraordinaire, and his wife Victoria (aka veebl). Great people, great times. I dragged them down to Boston so that we could hunt down this comic book shop I had found once by accident with daniels, and after we walked around quite a bit we managed to find it. Note to self: Kendall Square is nowhere near Kenmore Square. Need to remember that next time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave also handed me a kick-ass Voodoo3 card, which is awesome, since I&apos;ve been trying to hunt one down for a long time now. Problem is, it appears to be an AGP1 card, which would be great except that AGP1 cards do not in fact fit in AGP8 slots. So I can&apos;t use it in my badass desktop. It looks like I&apos;m going to have to build a machine with older parts. Good thing I still have 512M of RAM and a spare Athlon kicking around here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Steph moved out of the apartment again. She and Mo moved into a two-bedroom in the same complex, but we haven&apos;t hung out in weeks. It&apos;s kinda nice having the place all to myself again, now that it&apos;s actually quieted down around here. People have been over non-stop for weeks because I&apos;ve been hosting Battlestar Galactica fests with the miniseries DVDs. I think that BSG is probably the most ass-kicking show on TV right now, and I&apos;ve imparted this wisdom unto my coworkers and friends, even when they didn&apos;t necessarily want it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oh, speaking of forcing my will on others. So the whole reason that we went down to Boston was so that I could indoctrinate veebl with Transmetropolitan. I&apos;m happy to report that davej and veebl are both already huge fans of Bill Hicks, Invader Zim (and by extension, Jhonen Vasquez), and Ed Wood. Which means that Sam needs to come up here and visit me at some point, because I think we&apos;d all get along great.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have ordered the Canadian release of Ginger Snaps. If you&apos;re into really awesome B-movie style monster flicks, it&apos;s perfect and you should already own it. If you&apos;re not a fan of the genre, you must suck and that&apos;s why I don&apos;t talk to you. And if you are a fan but you don&apos;t know it, GET IT. It&apos;s a story about two loner sisters who make a suicide pact with eachother but one of them ends up being bitten by a werewolf. Their mother is played by Mimi Rogers (who is amazingly hot for an older woman) and she does a scary great job in her role. The rest of the movie is also filled with great moments, but I&apos;ll leave it to you to pick it up and find out what they are. I picked mine up from &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dv-depot.com/&quot;&gt;DV Depot&lt;/a&gt; - if you do go there, tell&apos;em that I sent you. (I have no idea what they&apos;ll do if you do, but I think it&apos;d be cool if a dozen people went and bought this DVD and put a comment in saying &apos;clee sent me&apos; - maybe they&apos;d give me some sort of freebie or something.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>i thought you were gonna adopt one of us</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/adopt_one_of_us.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2005 23:56 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;So on Thursday, I get a phone call around five in the evening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s my mom. I flip a coin and decide &quot;WTF, might as well answer it.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She says, &quot;I&apos;m at the airport. You should come pick me up.&quot; I respond with, &quot;Haha, mom. Very funny, but that&apos;d be &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; line, remember?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Backstory: Around Christmas, I was on the phone with the family and I tell my mom this plan that I&apos;ve been cooking for a few weeks, which was basically that I was going to neglect to inform anyone in advance of my plans to come visit. Meaning that, once I did show up, I&apos;d be totally unexpected and unannounced. It&apos;s more fun that way. I explained that the only notice that she&apos;d have would be my phone call from the airport, saying, &quot;Hey, you should come pick me up or something.&quot;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apparently, my mom and I think more alike than even I want to admit. She had already bought her ticket to come up here by the time that we had this conversation around the holidays. She&apos;s here now, sitting on the sofa near me, rocking out to Bon Jovi.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And there&apos;s food in the fridge again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Damn, I love having my mommy around.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>you&apos;re probably teeming with plague juice</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/teeming_with_plague_juice.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2005 02:33 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Wow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s been waaay too long since I updated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The holidays were relatively uneventful, as were the days leading up to them, so there wasn&apos;t really too much to blog about.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the past week has been complete insanity. Where should I start?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starting off: Kyle got here on December 28th. Seems like a short amount of time, and yet so long ago all at once. His arrival coincided with the arrival of my copy of a used copy of Final Fantasy III for the Super Nintendo (which is arguably one of the best video games of all time). We opted instead for the classic Legend of Zelda: A Link to the Past, however, and spent a few days playing that and fucking around with Super Metroid as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once my paycheck rolled in (on December 31st), I made sure to remember to write the rent check, and then Kyle and I rolled down to New York. We dropped my car off at my uncle Ed&apos;s place in Amityville and then took the train into the city where we walked around for a couple of hours trying to get close to Times Square for the ball dropping. We ended up about two blocks away, at the corner of 40th St and 7th Ave. Amazing time. I couldn&apos;t have imagined what a million people on the streets of New York City would look like, but I can say that it was absolute insanity. We then hooked up with Ray, Mo, and Dan at the corner of 38th and 7th and we walked around for a while hunting things to do. Had a pizza in Little Italy, then managed to make it back to Penn Station for a 5AM train back out to Amityville. Slept.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following day (the first of the new year, huzzah) we drove out to go meet up with Kyle&apos;s dad, who still lives on Long Island. Met a *ton* of Kyle&apos;s family. Had amazing Chinese food at the Golden Dragon. Slept at Kyle&apos;s dad&apos;s place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Woke up, had breakfast at a kick-ass diner. Kyle&apos;s little sister is shockingly bright, and only six years old. We left from there, and met up with Sharissa and our buddy The Cabeza in Middle Island. Had ice cream at Friendly&apos;s, went to Wal-mart, picked up &lt;b&gt;Shaun of the Dead&lt;/b&gt; (fucking brilliant, loved it), and then went to go see &lt;b&gt;Meet the Fockers&lt;/b&gt; at the theater. Tickets were $9.75 apiece (ow) and we didn&apos;t even think about popcorn or food. Sharissa talked her mom into letting us crash at her place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next day started, we spent some more time with Sharissa and then we had to leave to get back to my uncle&apos;s place in Amityville. Had dinner of leftover Chinese food and pizza. Slept there, then woke up before the sun to start the day since Ed and his family had to leave the house by 7:30AM and so we had to be out so they could lock up. Bummed around the island a bit, picked up some bagels that are so good they scared us, drove back over to the Longwood Public Library to see if it was open at 8:30. It wasn&apos;t. We brainstormed for a bit and decided to pick up some soda. Picked up said soda, went back to the car, decided to go check out our old elementary school and see if any of our old teachers were still there. Answer: Negative. Every single one of them has either retired or moved on to the middle or high schools. Kind of depressing, that. Then we went back to the library, as we&apos;d killed enough time for them to open up, and I promptly got a call from Vinny. We went over to his place, geeked out with more old-school video games and had a good time hanging out and catching up with his family. His mom got married a couple of weeks ago and failed to inform anyone. The wedding is August 19th. Have to go to that. From Vinny&apos;s, we drove back up here to NH, where we slept, bringing us to today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Woke up at about 1PM, finished off Zelda (damn, that game is still awesome even after all this time) and had some of the bagels we picked up. Stayed mostly comatose the whole day long, until Steph decided it was time to go get dinner. We had dinner at Pizzico, then I had to take Kyle to the airport.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All in all, a damned good time and a crazy hectic week. The only regret is, total hacking activity of the past week: zero.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hopefully now that I&apos;m back I&apos;ll get to kick things up again. Email was surprisingly merciful while I was gone, so there isn&apos;t that much to catch up on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;::yawns::&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All right, I&apos;m out. Later, everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>