<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>corner widgets 2</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/KDE/corner_widgets_2.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2004 06:19 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;so I was doing it wrong. ceebx&apos;s code works great. (I was checking for currentTab == 0 &amp;&amp; cornerWidget, but I needed to be checking for currentTab == 0 &amp;&amp; !cornerWidget. one simple little bug...)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;of course, I said I&apos;d probably commit this stuff last night. now I want to integrate a ConfigPage in with my commit so I can have a huge commit with new fun stuff in it... :)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;mmm. well, it&apos;s nice to have Konqueror drawing the tabwidget correctly now. it doesn&apos;t look so silly anymore.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>corner widgets</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/KDE/corner_widgets.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2004 01:35 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;got an email from ceebx tonight - this guy rules. not only is Plastik the single most visually attractive style I&apos;ve used (well, aside from the ones I&apos;ve written, of course ;) but he sends me suggestions for problems that he comes across.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;now, the current suggestion he sent me doesn&apos;t seem to be working just yet, but I&apos;m sure I&apos;ll get it to. I hate QTabWidgets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>jessica and intervention</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/jessica_and_intervention.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2004 01:07 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;the intervention didn&apos;t happen. Caitie got cold feet, chickened out, and didn&apos;t even show up until twenty minutes before Jessica left. I feel like shit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jessica really is too good for her boyfriend. that&apos;s really all there is too it. I wish I could have convinced Caitie to go through with it, but my persuasive skills aren&apos;t what they used to be, I guess. oh well... I tried, and I failed. it really does make me sad though.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>