<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>surprise revelation</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/surprise_revelation.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 30 Jun 2004 00:53 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;{lady friend}: no you&apos;re my examplar of what the guys i date have to live up to :-p &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&apos;m humbled. I had no idea that I was anywhere near that cool.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Of course, this means I&apos;m just going to be that much &lt;b&gt;more&lt;/b&gt; insufferable in the Real World, because I rock so much. But yeah, I was really surprised that someone out there thinks that of me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>drunken monkeys</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/drunken_monkeys.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2004 16:05 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Heh. I almost forgot that we went to go meet with a couple of Ximian guys in Cambridge last night. Ray, John Palmieri, Dan Reed and myself all met up right outside the T and we were completely pimped out in our stylish red fedoras (those hats rock). We had dinner at this cool place called CBC - can&apos;t remember what it stood for - and then we met the monkeys over at a pool hall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave Camp is a funny motherfucker.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And Luis Villa is also pretty funny, but in a more quiet sort of way. Dave is funny in an &quot;I&apos;m the asshole that everyone loves to hate&quot; way, which is fine with me. Upon seeing us in our (ridiculously sexy) red hats, he told us to get the hell out of his bar. We laughed, and then someone mentioned that I&apos;m the guy he should kick out since I work on KDE. (I think that it might&apos;ve been me who mentioned it, but anyway.) So then he looks at me and proceeds to tell me &quot;Ok, they&apos;re cool, but YOU definitely need to leave.&quot; And then we had a fun time bullshitting about various things, including the whole Novell/Ximian/SUSE craziness.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave&apos;s version of a meeting with one of our KDE guys over at SUSE in Germany: &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;So, what&apos;re you gonna do if they pick GNOME?&quot;&lt;br /&gt;&quot;I&apos;m going to quit.&quot; ::pause:: &quot;What&apos;re you going to do if they pick KDE?&quot;&lt;br /&gt;&quot;I&apos;m gonna quit.&quot;&lt;br /&gt;::silence::&lt;br /&gt;&quot;Well, cheers!&quot; ::drinking::&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Heh.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>wonder where all the socks came from</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/wonder_where_all_the_socks_came_from.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2004 15:57 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I&apos;m personally fine with broadcasting my personal life over the internet to whoever&apos;s interested. It&apos;s sort of an exhibitionist thrill, but I understand that it&apos;s definitely not for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Having said that, I&apos;ve got the good sense not to blog about anything &lt;i&gt;too&lt;/i&gt; personal on here, as I know that anybody could read it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As far as &quot;the goal of planetkde&quot; - the goal that I&apos;ve set for it is exactly what it says in the disclaimer. It&apos;s the aggregation of public weblogs written by KDE contributors; that means that if they only want me to feed from their KDE topic, then I will; but if they don&apos;t mind having the rest of their info on the site too, then I&apos;m fine with that as well. So long as the blog content isn&apos;t direct obvious flamebait, I&apos;ll have no reason to mess around with things. Also, although I think it sounds cool to rule with an iron fist, I&apos;m far too lazy to do that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, since this is actually a personal entry (and not a tech/KDE one) I have to say that I&apos;m super excited because my friend Steph is moving up here and she&apos;s leaving in less than three weeks! Seriously. My life just keeps on kicking more ass. On top of that, Daniel&apos;s coming up in three weeks and three days, and we&apos;re leaving for OLS on the seventeenth, I think. Everything rocks. And Red Hat is the coolest place to work, ever.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>ok, this sucks less</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/ok,_this_sucks_less.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2004 12:05 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Ah... I love it when things work out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, mere minutes after my last post, lyp pinged me on IRC and we sorted things out. He&apos;s uncomfortable with his personal posts being on Planet KDE anyway, which I totally understand, so he&apos;s set up a new RSS feed for KDE-related posts. And has thus been re-added to the blogroll, as has mornfall.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good times.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>this sucks</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/this_sucks.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 17 Jun 2004 11:32 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ve been friends with &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.lypanov.net&quot;&gt;lypanov&lt;/a&gt; (aka Alexander Kellet) for a while now; at least, I&apos;ve considered us friends for a while. He&apos;s a great guy, he&apos;s really cool, and we&apos;ve always gotten along pretty well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, he posted an entry to his blog stating that he was giving up on KDE, and immediately thereafter, he logged off of IRC (before I had a chance to ask him what was going on). Within the hour, I had received half a dozen emails asking me why our own developers were giving up on our project and if KDE had a future.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, I don&apos;t consider myself to be a fascist dictator by any means, but at the time the only options I saw were to leave things the way they were and field the questions, ask him to change his entry (which I vehemently disagree with), or to remove his blog temporarily until I had a chance to chat with him and find out what was going on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, as a result I&apos;ve been asked remove &lt;a href=&quot;http://mornfall.homeip.net/~mornfall/&quot;&gt;Peter Rockai&lt;/a&gt;&apos;s blog. Peter&apos;s also a really cool guy who I&apos;ve gotten along with pretty well so far, and he brought up a really good point - which is that I should have done this (replying in public about the issue) from the start. I wish that I had. Now apparently Alex doesn&apos;t want to be back anyway (which I can understand) and Peter is gone as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ugh. What does everyone else think? Feel free to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:clee@kde.org&quot;&gt;email me&lt;/a&gt; your thoughts, or if you&apos;ve got a blog syndicated here, feel free to post a reply on it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>going live</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/KDE/going_live.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 14 Jun 2004 09:06 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Well, it looks like &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.kde.org/&quot;&gt;KDE.org&lt;/a&gt; and even &lt;a href=&quot;http://planet.debian.net&quot;&gt;Planet Debian&lt;/a&gt; have picked up on the existence of my little project, so I guess it&apos;s time to officially say &quot;Yes, we&apos;re live!&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Disclaimers are up, layout is (mostly) finished, other planets have been linked, seats are in their upright positions... And we are live, ladies and gents!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now if only someone would fix up KBlog (or Tack! Tack needs love too!) Oh, and we need hackergotchi icons. Any artists want to volunteer?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>blog feeds</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/KDE/blog_feeds.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2004 22:23 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;In response to &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pycs.net/lateral/weblog/&quot;&gt;Roberto&apos;s&lt;/a&gt; query: If you have a blog with a working RSS feed (e.g., one that includes the &amp;lt;pubDate&amp;gt; tags) send an email to clee@kde.org with your name, what you hack on, and the URL of your RSS feed, and I&apos;ll add you to the blogroll here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hopefully Ian will fix up kdedevelopers.org soon so that I can start pulling those blog entries too.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>tack release</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/KDE/tack_release.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2004 08:21 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;With the advent of &lt;a href=&quot;http://planetkde.org/&quot;&gt;planet KDE&lt;/a&gt;, we need a decent blog posting utility for KDE. This isn&apos;t it, but it might become that utility if enough people send patches to me (or hey, you can always fork it!)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ladies and gentlemen, without further ado, I present to you:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://c133.org/files/tack-0.0.tar.bz2&quot;&gt;Tack 0.0&lt;/a&gt;, the most minimalist and feature-starved blog posting utility KDE has ever seen. It needs loving, lots of it, and as I&apos;m going to be on an airplane later on today I can&apos;t give it the loving it so deserves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So download it, marvel at its simplicity and lack of functionality, and then hack on it and send me patches so that it stops sucking so much.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is all.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>planet KDE</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/KDE/planet_kde.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2004 06:08 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I was discussing how addictive &lt;a href=&quot;http://planet.gnome.org/&quot;&gt;Planet GNOME&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://planet.debian.net/&quot;&gt;Planet Debian&lt;/a&gt; are on #kde-devel with a few KDE developers and we lamented the lack of a Planet KDE. However, unlike them, I actually decided to get up and do something about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Behold! &lt;a href=&quot;http://planetkde.org/&quot;&gt;Planet KDE&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yes. It&apos;s ugly. It&apos;s also fairly empty. Until &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.kdedevelopers.org/blog/geiseri&quot;&gt;Ian&lt;/a&gt; fixes up kdedevelopers.org (see how &lt;a href=&quot;http://planetkde.org/broken.html&quot;&gt;messed up&lt;/a&gt; the feeds are?) so that it includes &amp;lt;pubDate&amp;gt; tags so that the blog entries get sorted correctly, we&apos;re pretty lonely over here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The good news is, if you&apos;re a KDE developer with a blog on your own site, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:clee@kde.org&quot;&gt;mail me&lt;/a&gt; the URL of your properly-formed RSS feed, tell me what you do in KDE, and I&apos;ll add you to the blogroll as soon as possible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>I kick ass</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/fdo/i_kick_ass.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2004 22:21 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Tonight is rocking hardcore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I spent about twenty minutes autotooling the &apos;nv&apos; driver from the old monolithic X server tree, and convinced it to build under Daniel&apos;s Xizzle/Xorg tree.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After a bit more hacking around with the build system (to get it to properly generate the Makefiles in the nv dir, and to get the new NV driver module loaded into the libdrivers.a), it actually worked!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It loads the driver, and it sets the proper resolution, and everything!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now the only thing missing is composite support. Which is a little out of my league, but I have faith that the guys at Sun working on it (yeah, I&apos;m looking at you, Stu and Deron) will pull it off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Damn, this has been a good night.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>domain transfers</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/domain_transfers.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jun 2004 16:23 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ve had this domain for a while; I personally thought it was cute, and kind of a good tongue-in-cheek joke amongst my friends and myself, but it&apos;s about to expire, and so I&apos;m in the process of transferring the domain registry to another registrar. (Rick at &lt;a href=&quot;http://dns.vanrein.org/&quot;&gt;dns.vanrein.org&lt;/a&gt; is really cool, but I don&apos;t have e-gold, and his rates aren&apos;t the lowest... so since I&apos;m rather strapped for cash these days, I had to find someone cheaper. Of course, I can&apos;t afford to lose any email, either...)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;in other news, I&apos;ve been trying to grok a lot more design knowledge from a few guys with some really good taste. Namely, the Design Fab Five. Good stuff from them, and I like a lot of their ideas. Except for Flash - which I&apos;m not diametrically opposed to, but I just have no use for. So my site really is getting a redesign; I&apos;m not sure exactly what it&apos;ll end up looking like, but I&apos;ll leave the option for everyone to continue to use this particular design if they really like it. This one is a hybrid of a couple designs I saw on OSWD, plus a few custom modifications that I made myself.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>