<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>it gets all jiggly</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/jiggly.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2006 04:21 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I learned something interesting a few weeks ago and it just popped back into my mind so I decided to record it for my adoring fans.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Second-hand smoke really fucks with me. Savanah introduced me to a friend and we spent a few hours at said friend&apos;s apartment; they both did some pretty impressive chimney impersonations and I ended up feeling sick for days. My throat felt like it was on fire, and I kept coughing up chunks of ... I don&apos;t even know what. Maybe lung. My nose wouldn&apos;t stop running and I was constantly sneezing.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&apos;m not sure exactly how much later - maybe a week or so - I was at Cliff&apos;s place and we were hanging out. I lamented the effects that the second-hand smoke had on my throat, and Cliff empathized with me; apparently I&apos;m not the only one that second-hand smoke fucks with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, Cliff&apos;s throat was not ravaged and he was in fact feeling fine, so he jokingly suggested that we smoke some hookah. (For those of you playing along at home, no, I&apos;m not using code-words for drugs. We smoke &lt;a href=&quot;http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hookah&quot;&gt;hookahs&lt;/a&gt;, not bongs, and we smoke tobacco out of them.) I figured, at this point, what the hell could it hurt? Cliff prepared the hookah and I continued coughing up internal organs.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Soon, the hookah was ready to go - those things take like ten minutes or so to get ready if you&apos;re fast, and longer if you&apos;re not - and we started smoking. Almost immediately, I noticed something very strange - my nose stopped running.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was intrigued.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Several minutes later, I noticed that I had also not been coughing. My nose was still not running, and I was even able to breathe out of both nostrils. You might think that&apos;s a funny thing to notice, but trust me, you don&apos;t miss it until you can&apos;t do it anymore.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hours later, I was still feeling worlds better. I&apos;m not sure what the logical explanation here is, but first-hand smoke fixed every symptom introduced by my overexposure to the second-hand variety. This perplexes me, but I do not question feeling well; I just enjoy it.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>