<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>looking at laptops</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/looking_at_laptops.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 04 May 2004 03:06 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ve been looking at a few laptops lately. Apparently the model I&apos;ve been ogling - the hp nx7010 - is very much similar to the Compaq X1000 (which shouldn&apos;t be a surprise to anyone). I have decided that the specs that I want are:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ol&gt;&lt;li&gt;Centrino. Pentium M or bust, I say. (It&apos;s the only way I&apos;m likely to get any decent battery life out of a laptop these days.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Wide-screen 8:5 aspect ratio. I suspect that 1280x800 may be too small; 1440x900 seems about right, but I will probably love 1680x1050 as well, but the important thing is that it&apos;s wide-screen.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;I would really prefer it without an OS but the other two specs have so far made this look extremely unlikely, as the only manufacturers I&apos;ve seen happen to be stuck with nasty evil agreements with Microsoft. (see previous rant.)&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Oh, also. I need at least half a gig of RAM, a 40 gig hard drive, a mobility Radeon would be nice (since it seems like the mobile GeForce chips aren&apos;t that prevalent in the Centrino machines...), a DVD/CDRW combo drive, Firewire, and gigabit ethernet.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;br /&gt;Yeah, it sounds like what I want is basically a Powerbook, I know. Except that since I&apos;m going to be working at redhat, I get the feeling that an Apple laptop would be sort of ... bad karma.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We&apos;ll see what happens.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>