<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>world of warcrack</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/world_of_warcrack.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2005 20:59 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I attempted to hunt down a copy of World of Warcraft a few weeks ago, in vain.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My searches were fruitless. I went to several Wal-Marts, Targets, and Gamestops. All were completely devoid of World of Warcraft loving. This made me sad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I ended up going to go visit Tony (who I&apos;ll be dropping by to see again on the sixth for the Chinese New Year) and I crashed at his place after he, Rob, and I stayed up until way too late watching Battlestar Galactica at Rob&apos;s place. The following morning, we got up and I talked Tony into going to the Apple store. It wasn&apos;t that hard to convince him, actually. I just said &quot;We&apos;re going to the Apple Store,&quot; and he complied. Once there, I had the instant flash of realization that the wonderful bastards at Blizzard put the Mac and PC versions of their games on the same CDs. Those crazy fools. I searched for the gem and - lo and behold - there were FIVE copies of WoW. I picked mine up, made sure it wasn&apos;t some book or gift card (like Target had. For shame, Target! For shame.) and I carried it to the line at the register and bought it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The game is incredible. It&apos;s seriously just amazing. If only I had a decent video card, one that didn&apos;t overheat when I played it... And dealing with Windows is shitty.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Which is why I&apos;ve bought a &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.apple.com/macmini/&quot;&gt;dedicated World of Warcraft box&lt;/a&gt;. It hasn&apos;t arrived yet, which irks me. But it should be here &quot;on or before&quot; the seventeenth of February, according to Apple. Huzzah for that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That&apos;s about all that&apos;s new in the past few weeks. I&apos;ll attempt to blog more frequently - hey, I should dump my .plan on here sometime and see what people think - but it&apos;d probably be easier if I had my blogging app working again. Sounds like a fun project for tonight!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>the other british dave</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/the_other_british_dave.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2005 20:49 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Spent the entire weekend hanging out with Dave Jones, kernel slacker extraordinaire, and his wife Victoria (aka veebl). Great people, great times. I dragged them down to Boston so that we could hunt down this comic book shop I had found once by accident with daniels, and after we walked around quite a bit we managed to find it. Note to self: Kendall Square is nowhere near Kenmore Square. Need to remember that next time.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Dave also handed me a kick-ass Voodoo3 card, which is awesome, since I&apos;ve been trying to hunt one down for a long time now. Problem is, it appears to be an AGP1 card, which would be great except that AGP1 cards do not in fact fit in AGP8 slots. So I can&apos;t use it in my badass desktop. It looks like I&apos;m going to have to build a machine with older parts. Good thing I still have 512M of RAM and a spare Athlon kicking around here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Steph moved out of the apartment again. She and Mo moved into a two-bedroom in the same complex, but we haven&apos;t hung out in weeks. It&apos;s kinda nice having the place all to myself again, now that it&apos;s actually quieted down around here. People have been over non-stop for weeks because I&apos;ve been hosting Battlestar Galactica fests with the miniseries DVDs. I think that BSG is probably the most ass-kicking show on TV right now, and I&apos;ve imparted this wisdom unto my coworkers and friends, even when they didn&apos;t necessarily want it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oh, speaking of forcing my will on others. So the whole reason that we went down to Boston was so that I could indoctrinate veebl with Transmetropolitan. I&apos;m happy to report that davej and veebl are both already huge fans of Bill Hicks, Invader Zim (and by extension, Jhonen Vasquez), and Ed Wood. Which means that Sam needs to come up here and visit me at some point, because I think we&apos;d all get along great.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have ordered the Canadian release of Ginger Snaps. If you&apos;re into really awesome B-movie style monster flicks, it&apos;s perfect and you should already own it. If you&apos;re not a fan of the genre, you must suck and that&apos;s why I don&apos;t talk to you. And if you are a fan but you don&apos;t know it, GET IT. It&apos;s a story about two loner sisters who make a suicide pact with eachother but one of them ends up being bitten by a werewolf. Their mother is played by Mimi Rogers (who is amazingly hot for an older woman) and she does a scary great job in her role. The rest of the movie is also filled with great moments, but I&apos;ll leave it to you to pick it up and find out what they are. I picked mine up from &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.dv-depot.com/&quot;&gt;DV Depot&lt;/a&gt; - if you do go there, tell&apos;em that I sent you. (I have no idea what they&apos;ll do if you do, but I think it&apos;d be cool if a dozen people went and bought this DVD and put a comment in saying &apos;clee sent me&apos; - maybe they&apos;d give me some sort of freebie or something.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>i thought you were gonna adopt one of us</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/adopt_one_of_us.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2005 23:56 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;So on Thursday, I get a phone call around five in the evening.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s my mom. I flip a coin and decide &quot;WTF, might as well answer it.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She says, &quot;I&apos;m at the airport. You should come pick me up.&quot; I respond with, &quot;Haha, mom. Very funny, but that&apos;d be &lt;i&gt;my&lt;/i&gt; line, remember?&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Backstory: Around Christmas, I was on the phone with the family and I tell my mom this plan that I&apos;ve been cooking for a few weeks, which was basically that I was going to neglect to inform anyone in advance of my plans to come visit. Meaning that, once I did show up, I&apos;d be totally unexpected and unannounced. It&apos;s more fun that way. I explained that the only notice that she&apos;d have would be my phone call from the airport, saying, &quot;Hey, you should come pick me up or something.&quot;)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Apparently, my mom and I think more alike than even I want to admit. She had already bought her ticket to come up here by the time that we had this conversation around the holidays. She&apos;s here now, sitting on the sofa near me, rocking out to Bon Jovi.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And there&apos;s food in the fridge again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Damn, I love having my mommy around.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>you&apos;re probably teeming with plague juice</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/teeming_with_plague_juice.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jan 2005 02:33 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Wow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s been waaay too long since I updated.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The holidays were relatively uneventful, as were the days leading up to them, so there wasn&apos;t really too much to blog about.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the past week has been complete insanity. Where should I start?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Starting off: Kyle got here on December 28th. Seems like a short amount of time, and yet so long ago all at once. His arrival coincided with the arrival of my copy of a used copy of Final Fantasy III for the Super Nintendo (which is arguably one of the best video games of all time). We opted instead for the classic Legend of Zelda: A Link to the Past, however, and spent a few days playing that and fucking around with Super Metroid as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once my paycheck rolled in (on December 31st), I made sure to remember to write the rent check, and then Kyle and I rolled down to New York. We dropped my car off at my uncle Ed&apos;s place in Amityville and then took the train into the city where we walked around for a couple of hours trying to get close to Times Square for the ball dropping. We ended up about two blocks away, at the corner of 40th St and 7th Ave. Amazing time. I couldn&apos;t have imagined what a million people on the streets of New York City would look like, but I can say that it was absolute insanity. We then hooked up with Ray, Mo, and Dan at the corner of 38th and 7th and we walked around for a while hunting things to do. Had a pizza in Little Italy, then managed to make it back to Penn Station for a 5AM train back out to Amityville. Slept.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Following day (the first of the new year, huzzah) we drove out to go meet up with Kyle&apos;s dad, who still lives on Long Island. Met a *ton* of Kyle&apos;s family. Had amazing Chinese food at the Golden Dragon. Slept at Kyle&apos;s dad&apos;s place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Woke up, had breakfast at a kick-ass diner. Kyle&apos;s little sister is shockingly bright, and only six years old. We left from there, and met up with Sharissa and our buddy The Cabeza in Middle Island. Had ice cream at Friendly&apos;s, went to Wal-mart, picked up &lt;b&gt;Shaun of the Dead&lt;/b&gt; (fucking brilliant, loved it), and then went to go see &lt;b&gt;Meet the Fockers&lt;/b&gt; at the theater. Tickets were $9.75 apiece (ow) and we didn&apos;t even think about popcorn or food. Sharissa talked her mom into letting us crash at her place.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next day started, we spent some more time with Sharissa and then we had to leave to get back to my uncle&apos;s place in Amityville. Had dinner of leftover Chinese food and pizza. Slept there, then woke up before the sun to start the day since Ed and his family had to leave the house by 7:30AM and so we had to be out so they could lock up. Bummed around the island a bit, picked up some bagels that are so good they scared us, drove back over to the Longwood Public Library to see if it was open at 8:30. It wasn&apos;t. We brainstormed for a bit and decided to pick up some soda. Picked up said soda, went back to the car, decided to go check out our old elementary school and see if any of our old teachers were still there. Answer: Negative. Every single one of them has either retired or moved on to the middle or high schools. Kind of depressing, that. Then we went back to the library, as we&apos;d killed enough time for them to open up, and I promptly got a call from Vinny. We went over to his place, geeked out with more old-school video games and had a good time hanging out and catching up with his family. His mom got married a couple of weeks ago and failed to inform anyone. The wedding is August 19th. Have to go to that. From Vinny&apos;s, we drove back up here to NH, where we slept, bringing us to today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Woke up at about 1PM, finished off Zelda (damn, that game is still awesome even after all this time) and had some of the bagels we picked up. Stayed mostly comatose the whole day long, until Steph decided it was time to go get dinner. We had dinner at Pizzico, then I had to take Kyle to the airport.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All in all, a damned good time and a crazy hectic week. The only regret is, total hacking activity of the past week: zero.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hopefully now that I&apos;m back I&apos;ll get to kick things up again. Email was surprisingly merciful while I was gone, so there isn&apos;t that much to catch up on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;::yawns::&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All right, I&apos;m out. Later, everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>