<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>corner widgets 2</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/KDE/corner_widgets_2.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2004 06:19 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;so I was doing it wrong. ceebx&apos;s code works great. (I was checking for currentTab == 0 &amp;&amp; cornerWidget, but I needed to be checking for currentTab == 0 &amp;&amp; !cornerWidget. one simple little bug...)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;of course, I said I&apos;d probably commit this stuff last night. now I want to integrate a ConfigPage in with my commit so I can have a huge commit with new fun stuff in it... :)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;mmm. well, it&apos;s nice to have Konqueror drawing the tabwidget correctly now. it doesn&apos;t look so silly anymore.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>corner widgets</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/KDE/corner_widgets.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2004 01:35 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;got an email from ceebx tonight - this guy rules. not only is Plastik the single most visually attractive style I&apos;ve used (well, aside from the ones I&apos;ve written, of course ;) but he sends me suggestions for problems that he comes across.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;now, the current suggestion he sent me doesn&apos;t seem to be working just yet, but I&apos;m sure I&apos;ll get it to. I hate QTabWidgets.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>jessica and intervention</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/jessica_and_intervention.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jan 2004 01:07 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;the intervention didn&apos;t happen. Caitie got cold feet, chickened out, and didn&apos;t even show up until twenty minutes before Jessica left. I feel like shit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Jessica really is too good for her boyfriend. that&apos;s really all there is too it. I wish I could have convinced Caitie to go through with it, but my persuasive skills aren&apos;t what they used to be, I guess. oh well... I tried, and I failed. it really does make me sad though.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>resolutions</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/resolutions.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jan 2004 16:46 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;it&apos;s been almost a week since my last blog! damn. I resolved to make sure to update this more often. not even four weeks and I&apos;m already falling behind.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;yesterday was fun. Caitie, Nuge, Brandi, Josh, and I all went to Red Sea. Kevin was over there (surprise surprise!) and Cliff showed up eventually, as did Steph, It was like a party or something, almost. everybody&apos;s decided that they&apos;re going to throw me a huge going-away party, although the little details (like &quot;when&quot; and &quot;where&quot;) have yet to be decided. sounds like good fun though.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Steph took advantage of Brandi being there, and apologized to her. Or so she says. haven&apos;t heard Brandi&apos;s side of the story yet. still, it&apos;s nice to hear that Steph&apos;s trying to be less caustic. she got me a gift yesterday, too, completely unexpectedly. the Onion calendar. hooray! new Onion every day for the rest of the year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;that&apos;s about all. the last week hasn&apos;t been that interesting. tonight should be, though. Caitie and Nuge and I have finally agreed to do our intervention with Jessica. no idea how that&apos;s going to go, but ... it needs to be done. Jessica is a really great friend, and an amazing woman, and she deserves far better than what she&apos;s currently getting. anyway.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>st. anger</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/st._anger.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2004 00:57 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ve been really getting into Metallica&apos;s St. Anger lately. I don&apos;t know why. You can hate me now, I guess - I know that all of the TRUE METALLICA FANS hate anything more recent than the Black album (which was good, of course). I guess I&apos;m not a TRUE METALLICA FAN then. that, and of course anybody who likes Metallica must have hated Napster. I have some news for you people - Napster was cool, but most of the stuff that people had on there was shitty. Too many idiots with broken CD rippers made too many shitty single MP3 copies. The real draw for me with Napster was the fact that I could find people with similar music interests, not the quality of the songs. besides, Ogg Vorbis kicks MP3 ass.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;in other news, not much is going on. watched some old home videos with Steph tonight - vintage stuff from the summer before last. good times. we had dinner at NYPD. reminds me of how much I miss playing hockey. (Danny Schowe used to work there. I don&apos;t think he does anymore, sadly. He was on my hockey team back in high school though.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;also good: Radiohead&apos;s Hail it to the Thief. I don&apos;t know why but it feels like the whole album is different interpretations of the same emotion. I like it though. need to get my hands on some more of their stuff. I hear Kid A was pretty good.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>give me money</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/give_me_money.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2004 22:43 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Well, you don&apos;t have to of course. But if you like me, or you really really like me, or you like the work I do on KDE or you just have too much money, you can donate funds to &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.paypal.com/xclick/business=clee%40kde.org&amp;no_note=1&amp;tax=0&amp;currency_code=USD&quot;&gt;clee@kde.org via PayPal&lt;/a&gt;. I&apos;ll be putting a button up as well. hooray capitalism!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>rock star</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/KDE/rock_star.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jan 2004 21:34 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I got an email from a Linux distributor today asking me if I would mind going into some detail on my widget style experience. Hopefully my reply will make a good impression, since I&apos;ve done a pretty decent amount of work in this field; I think it&apos;d rock if I were hired as a consultant or contracted out to for development work.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Life can be funny. I never expected that my after-school hobby might eventually open up so many doors for me. It&apos;s not quite the same as being a rock star, but life could definitely be much worse.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>this is a test from my tack app</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/KDE/this_is_a_test_from_my_tack_app.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2004 07:52 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;hooray! I have a test app! :D&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>200 gig hard drive</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/200_gig_hard_drive.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2004 01:04 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;So I got a 200G hard drive today. My dad decided to buy it for me as payment for all of the work I&apos;ve been doing trying to get his printer working exactly the way he wants it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mmmmm. New hardware. I&apos;ve completed the move of my /home over to the new drive, and now it&apos;s just a matter of wiping the 20G drive with my operating systems on it and using the 40G drive that previously held /home as my new OS drive. (I can fit more operating systems in 40G than I can in 20G! WOOOHOOO!)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also, having the laser printer connected to the Mac works seamlessly with KDE over the network. I just pointed a KDE app at the Mac&apos;s IP, and it automatically grokked the print queue and even showed me both printers that have been connected to the Mac - nifty stuff. I love open source software.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(still have to make progress on some sort of a KDE-pyblosxom client. moving that to the top of the TODO, once I&apos;m done screwing with the hard drives.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>temet nosce</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/temet_nosce.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2004 00:53 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I got into a funny conversation with Steph about marriage (of all things) earlier. I have a friend who lives in Minnesota and we were chatting the other day - the gist of the conversation was that since I&apos;m going to Syracuse, and potentially staying for a while, and applying to work at S.U., I would be getting free tuition. I joked that it&apos;d be convenient for her to just marry me and move in with me so she could take advantage of the free tuition (in the event that I do stay in Syracuse and that I&apos;m working at S.U.).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Steph exploded when I told her about this, revealing much more than I think she intended. &quot;You can&apos;t just marry someone for convenience! That&apos;s completely the wrong reason to get married! What are you, retarded?&quot; Apparently Steph still believes that people should only get married if they&apos;re in love. I think that&apos;s pretty amusing, personally, just because it doesn&apos;t seem to be that common a view among the 20+ crowd that we&apos;re going to be joining this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Would I actually marry someone for convenience? I don&apos;t know. Would I do it just for sex? Nah. Would I do it for the convenience of a lower insurance premium? Probably not. But would I do it if I knew that it was someone who would put up with me and keep me company so I wouldn&apos;t have to be alone? That&apos;s the one I&apos;m not really too sure about. I hate being alone. I mean, I don&apos;t mind being left alone for a while if I&apos;m busy doing something important but I just don&apos;t enjoy being single.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Part of the problem, I think, is that I&apos;m not nearly as confident as Steph is that I&apos;m going to find that special someone. I mean, I don&apos;t think I&apos;m quite troll-like (well, as long as I shower and shave, that is), but I&apos;m not going to be featured on the cover of GQ anytime soon, and it&apos;s not like I go clubbing or anything. Not that I&apos;d necessarily want to date anybody that I might meet clubbing - that whole idea scares me. But I&apos;m not that attractive and I&apos;m not that social, and most of the women I&apos;m interested in aren&apos;t interested back. The few that I&apos;ve dated that have been interested in me for me have ended up cheating on me (or wanting to and thus ending the relationship) so I don&apos;t really feel quite so self-confident anymore. Am I self-doubting? No, because I think the whole concept of self-doubt involves insecurity and questioning things, while I&apos;m fairly sure of my lesser qualities. I also think that&apos;s one of the reasons I get a kick out of helping people - I feel better about myself when I know that I&apos;m having a positive effect on others. Which, I think, also explains my whole knight-in-shining-armor complex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Felt kind of weird to realize that I&apos;m the friend Steph calls when she&apos;s got &quot;alone time&quot; while she&apos;s up in Idaho. Yeah, definitely weird.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>setting up this blog</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/setting_up_this_blog.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2004 05:58 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;so pyblosxom is neat software. I like the whole filesystem-to-blog mapping.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I really should have gone to sleep a long time ago. I&apos;ll need to talk to DanielS about nifty things like blogging via email (which it sounds like he has working with his, and that&apos;s just neat) and I&apos;ll probably get working on a KDE blogging client too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;anyway. I&apos;m out for now. peace, everyone.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>And now for something completely the same.</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/And_now_for_something_completely_the_same.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jan 2004 04:44 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;So I just went through a fairly messy breakup with Mickey, who I&apos;d been with for well over a year and a half. It turns out that she slept with her (ex?)-best-friend Andrew back in October, and I found out about it just in time for Christmas. Great Christmas present.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ugh. I feel like an ass. I guess it&apos;s a good thing that it happened at this point instead of later on, down the road, after more wasted time and such. Still, it sucks. I hate being alone. I had almost conquered my adequacy issues for a while there, too. Not to mention my problems with trusting people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And then today I find out another great bit of news: Mickey&apos;s already got a new boyfriend. Way to go. I want her to be happy. I want to be happy too though, and this doesn&apos;t help me towards that goal at all. Two days ago she was swearing up and down that she didn&apos;t want to date anyone ever again and that she&apos;d wait forever for me to forgive her and then this turns up. Good times. I have no idea how long it&apos;ll take me to get over her. Steff and I only dated for three or four months, but it took me a year and a half before I was ready for another relationship; I&apos;m afraid of how long it might take before I&apos;m actually ready for the next one, if there&apos;ll even be a next one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(For those among you who don&apos;t know - Steff was my first serious girlfriend and Steph is her ex-best-friend. Steff and I don&apos;t talk. Steff and Steph don&apos;t talk. Steph and I talk all the time, and we&apos;re pretty good friends.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oh well. The road trip to Colorado was awesome. Hands-down the most fun I&apos;ve had in years. Steph is awesome. And I forgot just how well Kyle and I get along. He&apos;s a rarity, I think - a truly great friend, not just someone fun to hang out with but someone that I know would take a bullet for me and someone I&apos;d take do the same for without a second thought. You don&apos;t stumble across a friendship like that too often. Steph is completely head over heels for him, of course; and his girlfriend Krystal is also amazing. She&apos;s really cute, and she seems like a great match for him. I&apos;m glad for him - they make a good couple. Steph isn&apos;t so glad, as she&apos;s so into him, but she&apos;ll have to figure out some way of dealing with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Speaking of Steph, it turns out that her grandmother died a day or two after we got back from CO. Not cool. It kind of puts a shitty pall over the memory of the trip because we were sitting there having a grand ol&apos; time while her grandma was dying. Another reason for me to feel like an ass.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I love my keyboard. Logitech stuff hasn&apos;t impressed me this much in the past, but now I&apos;m thinking that my next keyboard purchase will probably also be a Logitech as well. I still like the Microsoft optical mice though.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;KDE stuff is always interesting. I got free access to the Lindows ISOs today by virtue of my being a KDE developer as well as eV member. I sent an email to Michael Robertson (CEO of Lindows and generally very cool guy) mentioning that I&apos;d be more than happy to work with Lindows to develop a distinctive and professional GUI widget style for them but I haven&apos;t heard anything back yet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>