<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>Geek Central</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/geek_central.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2004 13:25 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Heh. Just remembered this snippet of conversation between Steph and myself:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;clee:&lt;/b&gt; http://www.thinkgeek.com/oreilly/tshirts/5eb7/&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;clee:&lt;/b&gt; For me&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;clee:&lt;/b&gt; http://www.thinkgeek.com/oreilly/tshirts/6388/&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;clee:&lt;/b&gt; For you&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;steph:&lt;/b&gt; We should get those and wear them at the same time and then go out!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;clee:&lt;/b&gt; :D&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;steph:&lt;/b&gt; Geek Central&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;clee:&lt;/b&gt; That would be awesome :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;clee:&lt;/b&gt; And the best part, of course, would be us taking pictures, and then posting them on our blogs :D&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;We will have those shirts. Oh yes.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I scare myself sometimes.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>instant embarrassment</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/instant_embarrassment.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jul 2004 13:18 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Daniel and I originally planned on staying in Canada until Tuesday or so; instead, we left yesterday and got a head start. We made &lt;i&gt;excellent&lt;/i&gt; time on the trip home; it took just over five hours for us to make it from Ottawa to Nashua, including two stops for gas.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OLS registration: $250 CDN&lt;br /&gt;Hotel stay at Les Suites: $215/night, CDN&lt;br /&gt;Pizza at 2AM: $20 CDN&lt;br /&gt;Two tanks of gas: $40 USD&lt;br /&gt;The look on Steph&apos;s face when we showed up three days early: Priceless&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Incidentally, that Mastercard marketing campaign was simply stunning. Hooray for corporate marketing!)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seriously, though; the look on Steph&apos;s face was just awesome. The apartment is a total mess; she didn&apos;t do any laundry, and everything is awesome. Her hair looks dead sexy though. (She dyed it red, apparently just finishing the process before we got home.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;OLS rocked. Daniel and I both agreed that we definitely have to do it again next year, only next time 1) We&apos;re taking our time getting up there. Two or three days each way. There&apos;s too much fun stuff that we missed out on this time. And 2) Steph has gotta go with us. Maybe we can get her involved in some sort of documentation effort, or translation, or something; it doesn&apos;t really matter. I&apos;m sure we can get her involved in the community somehow, and once she is she&apos;ll have a valid reason for coming.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And one of the few things that sucked about OLS was not having Steph around. I really wasn&apos;t expecting to miss her that much, but I did.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now. Since we&apos;re back home, there&apos;s this rather large Netserver LXr Pro which needs an operating system. I&apos;ve got the idea into my head that I want LDAP user accounts and Kerberos passwords in the apartment, so we&apos;ll see. I need to get an OS booting on this thing first though, which looks like it may actually be easier said than done...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>qotd 07/24/04</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/qotd_0724.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jul 2004 04:12 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;From Josh: &quot;You give us mall employees hope&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(said after I told him the story of how I hit on Libby)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>ols rocks</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/ols_rocks.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jul 2004 02:51 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Daniel and I drove up with Chris Blizzard for OLS, and we&apos;ve been here since Sunday. The conference is kicking *major* ass, and I&apos;ve gotten to meet tons of awesome people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bourbon that Bdale and Keith picked up completely knocked me on my ass though. I was completely out of commission on Tuesday, and barely managed to recover for Wednesday&apos;s activities.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Canada. What more can I really say? Like home, but just different enough to fuck with me. It&apos;s cool here, though; the wifi from the balcony is sort of spotty, but otherwise the room is awesome. More alcohol than I thought could be consumed has been.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Trying to convince Steph to start blogging. No luck as of yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Daniel is cramming hard for some deadlines. Which sucks for him. I feel kind of weird, being alone out here on the balcony, knowing that everyone else is asleep already. Good time to blog, though.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Kind of missing home, oddly enough. Never been homesick like this, not since the parents moved me to Arizona. Also, my mind keeps wandering back to Libby.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;::sigh::&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Overall, though - surprising quantities of ass-kickery have shown up in my life lately, and I&apos;m still frankly quite shocked at it. If only life could be this badass all the time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>hottest. redhead. ever.</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/hottest_redhead_ever.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 18 Jul 2004 01:19 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Just got back from an awesome date with Libby. I met her at Hot Topic while &lt;a href=&quot;http://fooishbar.org/daniel/blog/&quot;&gt;Daniel&lt;/a&gt; and I were shopping for some ass-kicking Nintendo shirts - she works there. I hit on her and asked her for her phone number - which apparently caught her off-guard, as she actually gave me her real number - and we just had a pseudo-date tonight at Pizzeria Uno.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Reasons why Libby kicks ass: &lt;ol type=&quot;1&quot;&gt;&lt;li&gt;Redhead.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Cynical.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Killer sense of humor.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Gorgeous.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;SEXIEST. VOICE. EVER.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;She knows what Linux is.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ol&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are more, but I&apos;m stoked enough right now that I can hardly concentrate. I&apos;ll update more later on.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other news, Chris Blizzard is hitching a ride up to Ottawa with Daniel and myself. We&apos;re doing the road trip with Rik van Riel and his wife, as well as Dave Jones.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Life kicks so much ass that my cheeks are starting to hurt.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>hackergotchi head</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/hackergotchi_head.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2004 00:29 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;So I&apos;ve taken the time out of my day to gimp up a &lt;a href=&quot;http://c133.org/img/me-sexy.jpg&quot; title=&quot;Me, about as sexy as I get.&quot;&gt;picture&lt;/a&gt; of myself to use as a hackergotchi head. It&apos;s not a particularly great pic, but I figured it had the most potential for hackergotchi status.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I like the way it turned out. Any other guys here on Planet KDE, if you take the time out to do this, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:clee@kde.org&quot;&gt;send me the PNG file&lt;/a&gt; and I&apos;ll upload it and get it set for you so that you too can have a floating disembodied head.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you do decide to gimp yourself up then please note that the image should be about 64 pixels wide to fit properly. Anything from 60 to 80 pixels tall will work for the height, but let&apos;s try not to make the images _too_ large.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(And yes, I&apos;ll host the images here so that your web server won&apos;t melt.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>Sandro, read this</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/sandro_read_this.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Jul 2004 01:16 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Sandro Giessl: Your feed seems to be down. Can you fix it?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thanks.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>