<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>gah</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/gah.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2005 00:35 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I hate caffeine deprivation headaches.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(For those of you following from home, yes, I had successfully kicked my caffine habit but then I realized that not drinking it sucked. So I started drinking it again. And just now, I went a couple of days without - again - and all of a sudden I&apos;ve got the headaches. Fuck.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also, Smallville is still one of my favorite TV shows. I honestly can&apos;t decide if I like it more than Battlestar Galactica or not.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>congratulations, zack</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/KDE/congratulations_zack.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2005 17:07 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Major kudos to Zack Rusin for getting hired at Trolltech.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(Not like it should be a surprise to anyone, since Zack kicks ass and Trolltech also kicks ass.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This bodes extremely well for KDE4. World domination!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>qotd</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/qotd_brandi.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 24 Mar 2005 01:24 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;&quot;You are like, so much better than a bathroom stall.&quot;&lt;br /&gt;-Brandi&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>spin spin</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/fdo/spin_spin.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 21 Mar 2005 17:27 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.livejournal.com/users/spyderous/13259.html&quot;&gt;Donnie&lt;/a&gt;: &lt;a href=&quot;http://planetKDE.org/&quot;&gt;Planet KDE&lt;/a&gt;, and every ten minutes. I&apos;m thinking about changing it to update every fifteen, though. We&apos;re getting enough feeds that we&apos;re spending more time updating than idling.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>qotd</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/qotd_mar07.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2005 17:28 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;[mgalgoci] policy I&apos;d like to have set: &quot;When people ask for email aliases, the aliases are granted on the grounds that IS gets to decide what the alias is.&quot;&lt;br /&gt;[clee] mgalgoci: oh, oh! what&apos;s mine?&lt;br /&gt;[hp] clee: I think your native american name is he-who-hopes-to-get-laid-using-enterprise-groupware-solution&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>musings</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/musings.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2005 05:05 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s 5AM.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&apos;m blind, and it&apos;s dark. Music from Metal Gear Solid 3 floats through my apartment and yet I can still hear the drops of blood hitting the surface of the water as my nose drains.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Nosebleeds have been a pretty common occurrence for about as long as I can remember; I&apos;ve had them ever since I was a little kid. They&apos;ve started back up recently, after I had gone several months without having any. I&apos;m not sure exactly why but I think it might be somewhat related to drinking soda. (While I was caffeine-free for that six weeks or so, I didn&apos;t have a single nosebleed.) I&apos;ve recently started drinking the stuff again, since it&apos;s easier to drink it than not to, but I may have to rethink that choice in light of this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oh well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Speaking of Metal Gear Solid 3, I finally sat down and played through the rest of it. I had gotten farther along than I thought before I stopped playing it back in November, and the game is just amazing. I can&apos;t think of enough words to describe how much I enjoyed playing through this game.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>