<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>unexpected results</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/unexpected_results.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2005 00:35 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Red Hat, my employer, has a site license for VMware. (Well, either a site license, or an assload of Workstation licenses, I&apos;m not really sure what the details are.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I decided &quot;Hey, why not play with the new release? You&apos;ve got new hardware. Maybe VMware will run acceptably fast on it!&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Man, what a fucking brilliant idea that was.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Backstory: I haven&apos;t booted Windows in a few months, not since Doom3 came out and wasn&apos;t available initially on Linux. However, I have some shiny new devices in the new box, including a SATA DVD burner, which so far doesn&apos;t seem to work with Linux very well. Ubuntu&apos;s kernel enables SATA ATAPI support, which Jeff Garzik tells me is a bad naughty thing of them to do since it&apos;s not ready yet. Which results in my ability to *see* the drive on /dev/scd0, if the planets align properly, but I can&apos;t actually use it for much.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This machine doesn&apos;t have a floppy drive, since I&apos;m a cheap bastard, and I happen to agree with Apple on this one. Fuck floppies. They should have died a long time ago. I also refuse to run Windows XP - I bought and paid for Windows 2000, a long time ago in a galaxy far far away, and it&apos;s the last release of Windows that I really plan on ever using. Windows 2000, being rather old, has some deficiencies, however. Like not having SATA support in the installer (unless you load a driver from a floppy, which I don&apos;t have).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I think to myself, &quot;Hey! VMware! Raw disk support! It used to work pretty well, why not try doing an installation from a virtual machine into a physical disk? You can use the VM to download drivers, then create a new hardware profile, reboot into it, and maybe that&apos;ll work.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;HAHAHAHAA&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let&apos;s just say that this was probably the worst idea I&apos;ve had all night, even worse than eating that third slice of pizza. My partition table on /dev/hda now looks like this, thanks to VMware:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;pre&gt;Disk /dev/hda: 41.1 GB, 41174138880 bytes&lt;br /&gt;16 heads, 63 sectors/track, 79780 cylinders&lt;br /&gt;Units = cylinders of 1008 * 512 = 516096 bytes&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This doesn&apos;t look like a partition table&lt;br /&gt;Probably you selected the wrong device.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;   Device Boot      Start         End      Blocks   Id  System&lt;br /&gt;/dev/hda1   ?      216399     1904881   850995205   72  Unknown&lt;br /&gt;Partition 1 does not end on cylinder boundary.&lt;br /&gt;/dev/hda2   ?      723265     1262922   271987362   74  Unknown&lt;br /&gt;Partition 2 does not end on cylinder boundary.&lt;br /&gt;/dev/hda3   ?      167316      167316           0   65  Novell Netware 386&lt;br /&gt;Partition 3 does not end on cylinder boundary.&lt;br /&gt;/dev/hda4         2671568     2671619       25817+   0  Empty&lt;br /&gt;Partition 4 does not end on cylinder boundary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Partition table entries are not in disk order&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&apos;m not even sure what to say about that.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(For those of you wondering why I wanted to play with Windows in the first place - SATA DVD burner. I know that I can install Win2K drivers for the SATA chipset, and I know that the DVD burner will *probably* work there.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>