<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>#if 0</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/fdo/if_0.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 30 Dec 2005 01:21 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;There is a lot of really useless code sitting in Xorg today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was playing with a CVS checkout and noticed a large chunk of one of the source files was commented out with #if 0; so, this piqued my curiosity and I decided to figure out how many blocks of code are commented out with #if 0 in the server, driver, and lib trees.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The current count, in CVS HEAD, as of about five minutes ago:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;table&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;th&gt;module&lt;/th&gt;&lt;th&gt;blocks of #if 0 code&lt;/th&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;libs&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;56&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;server&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;408&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;tr&gt;&lt;td&gt;drivers&lt;/td&gt;&lt;td&gt;648&lt;/td&gt;&lt;/tr&gt;&lt;/table&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All combined, that&apos;s 1112 blocks of code completely disabled at compile time just sitting there in the tree.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Haven&apos;t bothered checking any of the other modules; I&apos;m sure there&apos;s more in apps but I don&apos;t really think it matters for docs or fonts. Still. That&apos;s a lot of useless crap.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>you know what to do</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/you_know_what_to_do.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2005 22:32 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;So, &lt;a href=&quot;http://livejournal.com/~ajaxxx/&quot;&gt;ajax&lt;/a&gt; and I are hanging out the other night.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He heads to the fridge to grab a Coke, and comes back with a serious expression on his face.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;[ajax] Well, we have a couple of options.&lt;br /&gt;[clee] What?&lt;br /&gt;[ajax] There&apos;s only one Coke left. So, we can-&lt;br /&gt;[clee] Fight. To the death.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good times. (Obviously, I won, since I&apos;m here to blog about it.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>tungsten e2</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/tungsten_e2.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2005 18:40 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;My Palm arrived yesterday, finally.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ve been playing with it, and it seems to be a really cool device, barring a few issues. It feels very solid, and I like that. What I dislike is the software.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don&apos;t get me wrong - I love PalmOS, but PalmOS 5 is trying to do things it&apos;s just not capable of and Graffiti 2 makes me want to throw my shiny new toy into a wall. For example, the hack that the PalmOS guys are using for showing focus selection? It breaks with at least half of the color themes that they ship on the device, because it doesn&apos;t draw the halo properly on the buttons. And the fact that I can&apos;t create my *own* color theme annoys me, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I &lt;b&gt;need&lt;/b&gt; to figure out some way to get Graffiti 1 working on this thing. I&apos;m using a demo version of TealScript for now but it&apos;s a little on the slow side and I don&apos;t really like the idea of paying $30 for it, especially since it&apos;s *not* a faithful reproduction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sync works great over Bluetooth to my Mac mini, which is pleasing. The pilot-xfer command-line utilities on Linux seem to work very well too, which is good; I haven&apos;t tried any other utilities yet, but I will soon.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>coincidence?</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/coincidence.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2005 02:59 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;ajax arrived a few minutes ago, and my inbox just hit 666 messages.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;hmmm.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>palm rant</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/palm_rant.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 09 Dec 2005 20:35 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I blogged last month about switching my phone to Vonage, which has gone swimmingly well. I&apos;m really happy with Vonage, in that I haven&apos;t had to deal with them at all because their product just works (which is so rare in our industry that it&apos;s scary, and I&apos;m sad that I even find it noticeable that I&apos;m commenting on it), and also in that the features they provide seem to work really well. Being able to check my voicemail from the web is totally badass.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That said, since I no longer have a cell phone to keep my address book on, I decided to pick up a Palm once more. After checking out a few models and consulting with coworkers, I decided to pick up the &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.palm.com/us/products/handhelds/tungsten-e2/&quot;&gt;Tungsten E2&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I put my order in on Tuesday, December 6th, and I made sure to select &apos;Overnight shipping&apos; because I&apos;m an impatient bastard and I want it &lt;b&gt;now&lt;/b&gt;. I would&apos;ve gone into a store to buy it, but it came with a free 128MB MMC flash card when I bought it online from Palm, and like a sucker, I decided to go for the freebie.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(I also noticed, just after submitting my order, that Amazon was selling the same exact handheld, sans the 128MB flash card, for $150. D&apos;oh.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just got a mail from Palm, &lt;b&gt;today&lt;/b&gt;, informing me that my order has been shipped.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I won&apos;t have it until Monday; even if UPS does deliver it tomorrow, I had it scheduled for an office delivery since I expected to be at work, and I&apos;m not planning on going in to the office tomorrow.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In other words, by the time I get it, it will have been almost a week since I placed the order. With &quot;Overnight&quot; shipping.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>