<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>lseek(fd, 0x5c, SEEK_SET)</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/redhat/lseek_0x5c.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2005 17:49 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Our Intel rep managed to secure me an 802.11a/b/g mini-PCI card for my ThinkPad. Direct from Intel. Totally sweet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Somehow managed to get the ThinkPad apart, and dropped in the new card, and connected the antennae, and turned it on, and was greeted rather rudely by two beeps and the infamous Error 1802.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was prepared for this though. I expected to spend the rest of the day hacking around IBM&apos;s evil authorized-miniPCI-card whitelist and being otherwise 1337 just like mjg59. But instead, I found the source for a neat little hack that resets part of the nvram to a magic value and disables the whitelist check.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All this means for those of you who don&apos;t speak Geek is that I overrode some IBM stupidity and made my hardware work the way it should. Which should have been much easier, but hey, this is Linux, and we like things like lseek(fd, 0x5c, SEEK_SET) just fine.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>oh! and chainsaw hands!</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/redhat/oh_and_chainsaw_hands.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 30 Nov 2004 03:36 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Well, ok, no chainsaw hands, but I got my replacement laptop from work today. It&apos;s an X31 - smaller and sexier than my old T41, which was stolen from my car while I slept.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Don&apos;t think I&apos;ll be leaving this one in the car. Ever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But yeah, I&apos;m excited. FC3 actually isn&apos;t as bad as previous releases, so I&apos;m keeping it on there... I&apos;m probably going to see about taking over those KDE specfiles so I can have less-shitty KDE packages on Fedora, but we&apos;ll see. Don&apos;t want to go around making promises and disappointing people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I should really do a TODO one of these days and list out the stuff I need to take care of. Like that pyblosxom plugin. Damn.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>status 2004/10/07</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/redhat/status_2004_10_07.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2004 17:59 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Damn. The past week has been awesome.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Did the functional testing and RHNQA on a KDE errata here.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Filed bugs against gnome-panel, evolution-data-server, bonobo-activation-server, and ran into a terribly amusing metacity crasher.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Did the functional testing on an ugly cyrus-sasl vulnerability.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Did a *new* round of functional testing on a bug caused by the fix to the ugly cyrus-sasl vulnerability.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Pushed a release of redhat-artwork sometime last week anyway.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Continued hacking on the Qt port of BlueCurve.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All in all, dangerously productive. Not to mention keeping track of email and IRC.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>hooray errata</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/redhat/hooray_errata.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2004 17:00 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;ugh. Errata suck.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;that is all.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>good discussion</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/redhat/good_discussion.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2004 14:02 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Sat down with Ed and Zack yesterday and basically did a mind-meld; we had an hour-plus-long braindump session where I let loose all of the ideas, concerns, and issues that I&apos;ve been thinking about as far as desktop QA goes here at Red Hat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;John Flanagan dropped in towards the end of it, and he seems to be quite open to a lot of our ideas, which is awesome. Hopefully we can get the budget/machines allocated to implement the desktop testing lab that we want to set up; that would be perfect.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Number of times I&apos;ve forgotten my cardkey at the new office: Two&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Number of days since someone has passed out in the bathroom: Nine&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>