<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>gstreamer hacking</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/gstreamer_hacking.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2004 06:27 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;So mpyne had implemented a somewhat working SPC plugin for GStreamer which was pretty limited and somewhat useless. (As he admitted :)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His version had a hardcoded path to the SPC file, didn&apos;t work as a filter - just as a src - and was performing quite strangely on his system for some reason. I&apos;ve since rewritten it (from scratch) as a filter and not a src. It works on my system, kind of. I haven&apos;t gotten the typefind implementation done yet, and it&apos;s pretty fragile at the moment - I haven&apos;t figured out exactly why, but somehow removing a printf from the spc_setup function causes the plugin to segfault (I think LoadSPCFile may be doing something strange, but I&apos;m not sure...)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you have tla installed, you can do:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;pre&gt;tla register-archive http://c133.org/arch/&lt;br /&gt;tla get clee@kde.org--2004/gst-spc--filter--0 gst-spc&lt;/pre&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you don&apos;t have tla, you can try poking around on the site but seeing as how things aren&apos;t quite ready for mass consumption, I&apos;m not making any releases just yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now, to go take a shower. All of those &apos;g&apos;s and &apos;_&apos;s make me feel so dirty.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>I also have the orphans wet his bed while he&apos;s sleeping</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/i_also_have_the_orphans_wet_his_bed_while_hes_sleeping.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2004 06:20 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;It strikes me that I should note that I&apos;m now caffeine-free, and have been since the day after Thanksgiving. Which, by my reckoning, puts me on Day 11 of Operation Cold Turkey.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The funny thing is, I sort of quit by accident. I didn&apos;t really mean to stop drinking soda; I just sort of ran out, and then after I&apos;d had some pretty nasty headaches for a few days I realized that I had been going without soda for a few days. By the sixth day, the headaches were pretty much gone, and I&apos;m feeling pretty good about not drinking that stuff at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Others have mentioned that they have lost surprising amounts of weight simply by not drinking soda anymore. I&apos;m interested to see if this proves true for me as well.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>