<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>apartment hunting</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/apartment_hunting.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2004 07:50 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Have to go apartment hunting today. (I&apos;m in Boston for the week, looking at the area and seeing what&apos;s around here.) Basically, it looks like I&apos;m going to get face-raped by someone with a running start. A grand a month for a one-bedroom... it makes me want to cry.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oh well. This is a good problem to have. Much better than the &quot;homeless, jobless, and starving&quot; problem I was facing a few months ago. Although if I can&apos;t find a place for a low-enough price, I may be facing that problem again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On the bright side of things, the X Developers Conference starts tomorrow and that should be a blast.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>oil change</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/oil_change.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2004 11:13 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Changed the oil on my car this morning. Heading up to Boston today to go look for an apartment/housing, as well as to go to the X Developers Conference - hooray!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Something about doing an oil change is satisfying. I don&apos;t know exactly what it is, though. Just feels good. I&apos;m also glad to note that my car appears to not be burning oil, which may have something to do with my satisfaction.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oh, and I got hired by Red Hat.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>new jeans</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/new_jeans.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2004 01:37 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;My jeans rock, especially since they&apos;re these $10 jeans that I can beat the living shit out of and kick ass in. And they look badass on me, too, because they make my ass look hot. Which is no easy feat, but they do. I want my own ass at this point. It really looks that hot. If I saw my ass in these jeans, walking down the street, I&apos;d be like &quot;DAMN BITCH, THAT IS SOME FINE ASS YOU&apos;VE GOT&quot; and then when I turned around I&apos;d smack myself in the face and say &quot;What the fuck did you just say, bitch?&quot; And then I&apos;d kick my own ass all over the place, Tyler Durden style.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>evil plots</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/evil_plots.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2004 05:49 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Got a phone call from Brandi for the first time in weeks. Scared the shit out of me, as I had almost given up on her ever calling me again, since she does it so infrequently. I tortured her with descriptions of delicious buffalo beef. She wasn&apos;t amused, but I took great pleasure in it. When she finally gets up here, I&apos;m going to have to make sure to stock up. We&apos;re talking five pounds, easy, of buffalo meat. Mmmm. Buffalo meat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you still haven&apos;t tried it, you&apos;re probably a terrorist, or at least a vegetarian, which is just about as bad in my book. I feel like I should reiterate a point that I&apos;ve been making to my friends - for some reason, the women seem to take particular offense to this one, but hear me out. I would eat (cooked) baby seals if they tasted good. I don&apos;t care how cute they are; if they tasted good, I&apos;d be sitting down at the table with a fork and knife ready and waiting. Determining your willingness to eat an animal based on how cute it looks while it&apos;s alive is total bullshit, so stop doing it. Base your willingness to eat animals on how good they taste. (For example, I don&apos;t think that buffalo are significantly far from cows on the cuteness scale, but I&apos;ll tell you what.... I&apos;d eat buffalo over cow any day of the week, that&apos;s for damned sure.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The only depressing thing about buffalo meat is the price tag. I mean, it is definitely well worth the $5/pound price, but I wish it were cheaper anyway. Anyway, I&apos;m about to collapse, as it&apos;s getting light outside again, which means that it&apos;s time for me to go to sleep.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>invincible!</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/invincible.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2004 05:41 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I feel like the Russian hacker from Goldeneye. I AM INVINCIBLE! Over the course of one day, managed to wrangle IE into actually rendering my site halfway decently (which it should&apos;ve done in the first place), and also finally figured out a solution to an annoying problem with Apache and customized header/footer templates for automatic indexing. If that doesn&apos;t make sense to you, good.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other random things of coolness: Xcode has amazingly well-integrated CVS support. Apple kicks ass. Also, Safari kicks ass. I like Apple&apos;s implementation of the CSS2 text-shadow property in KHTML. I&apos;m also thinking about redesigning my site once more since I&apos;ve had the current design up for over a year now, and I&apos;m bored with it. It&apos;s a pain in the arse, especially for cross-browser compatibility, and I&apos;m itching to try out a few other look&apos;n&apos;feel combinations. DanielS has suggested that I should try to become a DD. I find this amusing, mostly because of how many discussions I&apos;ve had with DanielS where I have ranted about how much I hate Debian. Good times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;update: &lt;a href=&quot;http://c133.org/files/&quot;&gt;check out&lt;/a&gt; the customized output that I struggled for hours to achieve! Marvel at how much less cool it is than it should be!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>speaking of challenges</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/speaking_of_challenges.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2004 03:13 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I hate Internet Explorer. If you happen to be unfortunate enough to be using it, please, consider either upgrading to &lt;a href=&quot;http://mozilla.org/firefox/&quot;&gt;Firefox&lt;/a&gt; or convincing the people in charge over in IT to give it a shot. Firefox actually supports web standards - those neat things that make it possible for people to write all sorts of really neat web pages, without having to resort to evil nasty hacks.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have no idea what this page looks like under IE5. My closest guess would be that it looks like a plate full of ass, and if it does, then too bad. There are at least a half dozen other web browsers you can use that will render this site properly, and if all else fails you could always upgrade to IE6 since that works for now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the future, my &quot;compatibility&quot; with IE is going to consist of hiding things that the browser doesn&apos;t understand, instead of trying to get it to work.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>linux lives</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/linux_lives.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2004 00:44 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I love MacOS X. I don&apos;t mince words about it; the UI is gorgeous, simple, to-the-point, and I love it. I love Linux as well, but mainly because it&apos;s usually a challenge to get working right. After getting particularly bored the other day, and I thought to myself &quot;You know, self, this iMac works entirely too well.&quot; Seven hours later, Gentoo is up and (mostly) running.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Major props out to the guys who wrote parted, the guy who wrote the patches to parted to let it resize HFS+ filesystems without destroying data (if I ever meet you, I owe you a beer), and whoever wrote the driver for reading HFS+ volumes under Linux. All of this stuff makes using Linux on a Mac a much more pleasant experience.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Back in OS X land, though, the guys who I&apos;m the most impressed with are the team behind &lt;a href=&quot;http://colloquy.info/&quot;&gt;Colloquy&lt;/a&gt; which is hands-down, the single coolest Open Source application I&apos;ve seen on OS X yet. I&apos;ve seen a few other apps that I consider to have great user interfaces, but Colloquy is the only Open Source one. These guys are seriously awesome.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>sync script</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/sync_scrypt.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 15 Apr 2004 00:30 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I&apos;m on IRC the other day and my pal Daniel asks me if I&apos;d be interested in taking care of a sysadmin task for him on the freedesktop.org box (pdx). I wasn&apos;t doing anything so I said &quot;Sure, what is it?&quot; and he tells me he needs a script to:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Copy over the entire CVS tree from the CVSROOT&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Check out the latest code from each module in each CVS tree, and package it up&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;Also, pants&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I wrote it. It&apos;s neat. Hadn&apos;t done any shell scripting in a while, but this was relaxing and it gave me a chance to exercise some of my skills, which is always good.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>buffalo</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/buffalo.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 14 Apr 2004 18:50 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;so for all of you out there who have yet to experience the absolutely delicious taste of buffalo meat: I pity you. and for all of you who refuse to partake in such delicious food, I have no clue what&apos;s wrong with you, but I will &lt;a href=&quot;http://maddox.xmission.com/sponsor.html&quot;&gt;sponsor you&lt;/a&gt; if necessary.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;in other news, I&apos;m extrememly psyched. I don&apos;t want to jinx myself yet but there is a potential job prospect that I&apos;m very excited about. I&apos;ll announce more if something comes of it. that&apos;s all for now.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;oh, and also... badger.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>why are women evil?</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/why_are_women_evil.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2004 18:30 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;ok, I have a problem. I have a problem with women, specifically. I won&apos;t name any names but I know you&apos;re reading this out there, and this entry is all because of YOU.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;with that said, what the hell? I move to NY and all of a sudden, it&apos;s like &quot;Hey, you know... It&apos;s really too bad that you&apos;re in NY. And it&apos;s too bad that I have a boyfriend.&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;as if that&apos;s not bad enough, then it becomes &quot;Oh... well, I guess since you&apos;re in NY I can tell you that I did like you. hahaha! Doesn&apos;t that suck? You&apos;re 2500 miles away! And you can&apos;t do anything about it! But I do have a boyfriend anyway. Still...&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;so. completely. uncool.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&apos;m going to be beating myself over this for weeks. I can tell.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;maybe Josh has the right idea. although apparently, the same sort of thing happened to him after he went gay - only it became &quot;Hey, you know... It&apos;s really too bad that you&apos;re gay. I really liked you.&quot; &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I mean, seriously. I&apos;m not gay, and I don&apos;t think I ever could be, but you women are all evil.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>qotd</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/qotd.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2004 20:23 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;today&apos;s quote (from Tia):&lt;br /&gt;&quot;hell if i would have known that you were moving i would have handcuffed you to a bed and stuck you in a basement somewhere so you couldn&apos;t leave&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;good to know that I have friends who would abduct me and keep me in a basement. definitely good to know.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>interviews</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/interviews.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2004 20:22 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I went to Boston on Wednesday last week for an interview that I had at a community health center in the city. I got a call the same day from Red Hat asking if I wanted to come in for an interview the next day, so I told them &quot;Of course!&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;the interview went great! I had the most fun I&apos;ve ever had interviewing. I got to meet a bunch of cool guys and I had a blast chatting with them, about all sorts of stuff. they had me show up at 10AM and I was supposed to be done by 3, but they kept me until a little after 4. which hopefully is a good sign, but I don&apos;t want to get my hopes _too_ far up.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;the hospital was basically a dead end, though. they don&apos;t have any positions for the IS department, but they swore that they would call me as soon as they do. they did seem to be pretty impressed though, so I think it went well even if nothing comes of it. it&apos;s experience, anyway. which is always good.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>updates</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/updates.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Apr 2004 19:45 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;so, where to begin - it&apos;s been way too long since I wrote anything down; my apologies to anyone out there reading but I haven&apos;t had nearly as much internet access as usual lately, and I can&apos;t seem to find any decent blogging software for OS X so I may end up having to write my own.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;in other news.... Steph has decided not to move out here. shocking, I know. it&apos;s actually kind of sad, because she&apos;s really cool, and I was kinda looking forward to her moving out here. on the other hand, it&apos;s rather freeing, and I realized the other day that I&apos;m officially more free right now, at this very moment, than I&apos;ve ever been before in my life. I have no responsibilities to anyone, really - I have no obligations to maintain, no relationships holding me down or keeping me from doing what I want, and it&apos;s sort of a scary place to be. hopefully things will firm up a bit soon; it&apos;s an interesting place to be at, though.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;have been going to interviews and submitting the resume at tons of places up here. no solid results yet, unfortunately.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>