<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>implementing ideas</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/implementing_ideas.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2006 07:02 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I like getting around to implementing the various ideas that I bounce back and forth inside my skull.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of those ideas that I had for a long time was to solder a PS/2-&amp;gt;USB converter directly into an IBM Model M keyboard, along with a USB plug so that I could just swap out USB cables to plug the keyboard into the computer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.flickr.com/photos/12031124@N00/sets/72157594346862373/&quot;&gt;I have finally done that&lt;/a&gt;, after some &lt;a href=&quot;http://zevv.nl/experiments/ibm-usb/&quot;&gt;inspiration from zevv&lt;/a&gt;, a few choice purchases at Fry&apos;s Electronics, and a few borrowed parts from my friend Cliff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have to say, this kicks way more ass than even I had hoped. (ajax, eat your heart out.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still on the list:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;finish the Qt4 frontend for HandBrake&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;write my own email client that doesn&apos;t suck balls&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;write my own AIM client that doesn&apos;t suck balls&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;hack up some apps for Qtopia/Opie/whatever for my shiny new iPaq 3670&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know there&apos;s more than that, but those are the ones that are currently taking up the most brainspace, so I&apos;m going to have to get to them sometime.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Due to United Airlines sucking balls, &lt;a href=&quot;http://airlied.livejournal.com/&quot;&gt;Dave Airlie&lt;/a&gt; crashed at my place last night after they called back and cancelled his flight from SFO to Sydney. I&apos;ve said this before, although maybe not on this blog, but United are a bunch of cockbags. They have fucked up at least one leg of every single trip of mine that they&apos;ve ever been involved in. In any case, I know far too many foreigners named Dave.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also, I&apos;ve been growing &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.flickr.com/photos/12031124@N00/280500553/&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; out for the first time ever. Looks like I&apos;m going to have to update my various avatars...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>screeching handbrake</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/screeching_handbrake.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2006 09:16 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I really love it when I can easily find something that bothers me in a piece of software, dive into the source, and start fixing things.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That&apos;s what I&apos;ve been doing lately with this &lt;a href=&quot;http://handbrake.m0k.org/&quot;&gt;little DVD ripping app called HandBrake&lt;/a&gt; - it&apos;s a cross-platform GPL DVD ripper that makes it almost painfully easy to take a movie from a DVD and turn it into a file that you can watch whenever the need strikes you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are some problems, though. Right off the bat, there is the issue that (when ripping a DVD) libdvdread spews out hundreds of lines of output, warning me that a value isn&apos;t 0 and it should be. It&apos;s not fatal, but it certainly is annoying, so I whipped up &lt;a href=&quot;http://c133.org/tmp/libhb-dvd.diff&quot;&gt;this patch&lt;/a&gt; up to fix it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also, I don&apos;t have a video iPod at the moment, or a Sony PSP (and I don&apos;t see myself buying the latter anytime soon, but you know... if one were to fall into my lap, I&apos;d probably use it and enjoy the hell out of it.) Anyway, not owning one of these devices, I&apos;m more interested in HandBrake as a way to make high-quality compressed archives of my DVD movies that I can watch on the HDTV in the living room. There&apos;s a problem, though; HandBrake scales the picture by default as it transcodes it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://c133.org/tmp/enc-pixelratio.diff&quot;&gt;Not anymore&lt;/a&gt;, it doesn&apos;t. Now it has support for (optionally) embedding the anamorphic pixel ratio into the output file, and can preserve the original DVD video frames. Which means, with x264 at least, a reasonable performance increase of about 15%. Not too shabby!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, the only GUIs for HandBrake are on Mac OS X and BeOS. Now, I love BeOS. Haven&apos;t used it in years, though, and I don&apos;t even think it&apos;ll run on my hardware; Haiku still isn&apos;t quite there yet, either, but I&apos;m keeping tabs on it. What I really wanted is a Linux UI for HandBrake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, I&apos;ve been hacking on one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://c133.org/qhandbrake-1.png&quot; alt=&quot;Qt4 HandBrake UI&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned for more on this...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>aoe is hotness</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/aoe_is_hotness.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2006 05:03 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ve been playing with ATA over Ethernet on my home network and I have to say, it is pretty damn sweet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In fact, it would be absolutely perfect if I could use AOE to share drives to my media center, and then use ZFS on that machine. Unfortunately, Linux doesn&apos;t have ZFS, and OpenSolaris doesn&apos;t seem to have AOE yet. (The Coraid site has a Solaris driver, and they claim it works on Solaris 7+, but there is no source and I don&apos;t happen to have an OpenSolaris machine to test it on at the moment.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But - the ability to pool together all of my disparate disks into one gigantic volume is awesome. It&apos;s like Voltron, but with hard drives instead of robots.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>insert the sound of a jaw dropping</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/sound_of_a_jaw_dropping.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2006 04:56 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Definitely picking up one of &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.hasbro.com/pl/page.viewproduct/product_id.17889/dn/nerf/default.cfm&quot; alt=&quot;nerf. sniper rifle. oh yes.&quot; /&gt;these&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>