<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>evil plots</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/evil_plots.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2004 05:49 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Got a phone call from Brandi for the first time in weeks. Scared the shit out of me, as I had almost given up on her ever calling me again, since she does it so infrequently. I tortured her with descriptions of delicious buffalo beef. She wasn&apos;t amused, but I took great pleasure in it. When she finally gets up here, I&apos;m going to have to make sure to stock up. We&apos;re talking five pounds, easy, of buffalo meat. Mmmm. Buffalo meat.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you still haven&apos;t tried it, you&apos;re probably a terrorist, or at least a vegetarian, which is just about as bad in my book. I feel like I should reiterate a point that I&apos;ve been making to my friends - for some reason, the women seem to take particular offense to this one, but hear me out. I would eat (cooked) baby seals if they tasted good. I don&apos;t care how cute they are; if they tasted good, I&apos;d be sitting down at the table with a fork and knife ready and waiting. Determining your willingness to eat an animal based on how cute it looks while it&apos;s alive is total bullshit, so stop doing it. Base your willingness to eat animals on how good they taste. (For example, I don&apos;t think that buffalo are significantly far from cows on the cuteness scale, but I&apos;ll tell you what.... I&apos;d eat buffalo over cow any day of the week, that&apos;s for damned sure.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The only depressing thing about buffalo meat is the price tag. I mean, it is definitely well worth the $5/pound price, but I wish it were cheaper anyway. Anyway, I&apos;m about to collapse, as it&apos;s getting light outside again, which means that it&apos;s time for me to go to sleep.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>invincible!</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/invincible.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 17 Apr 2004 05:41 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I feel like the Russian hacker from Goldeneye. I AM INVINCIBLE! Over the course of one day, managed to wrangle IE into actually rendering my site halfway decently (which it should&apos;ve done in the first place), and also finally figured out a solution to an annoying problem with Apache and customized header/footer templates for automatic indexing. If that doesn&apos;t make sense to you, good.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Other random things of coolness: Xcode has amazingly well-integrated CVS support. Apple kicks ass. Also, Safari kicks ass. I like Apple&apos;s implementation of the CSS2 text-shadow property in KHTML. I&apos;m also thinking about redesigning my site once more since I&apos;ve had the current design up for over a year now, and I&apos;m bored with it. It&apos;s a pain in the arse, especially for cross-browser compatibility, and I&apos;m itching to try out a few other look&apos;n&apos;feel combinations. DanielS has suggested that I should try to become a DD. I find this amusing, mostly because of how many discussions I&apos;ve had with DanielS where I have ranted about how much I hate Debian. Good times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;update: &lt;a href=&quot;http://c133.org/files/&quot;&gt;check out&lt;/a&gt; the customized output that I struggled for hours to achieve! Marvel at how much less cool it is than it should be!&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>