<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>screeching handbrake</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/screeching_handbrake.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 22 Oct 2006 09:16 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I really love it when I can easily find something that bothers me in a piece of software, dive into the source, and start fixing things.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That&apos;s what I&apos;ve been doing lately with this &lt;a href=&quot;http://handbrake.m0k.org/&quot;&gt;little DVD ripping app called HandBrake&lt;/a&gt; - it&apos;s a cross-platform GPL DVD ripper that makes it almost painfully easy to take a movie from a DVD and turn it into a file that you can watch whenever the need strikes you.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There are some problems, though. Right off the bat, there is the issue that (when ripping a DVD) libdvdread spews out hundreds of lines of output, warning me that a value isn&apos;t 0 and it should be. It&apos;s not fatal, but it certainly is annoying, so I whipped up &lt;a href=&quot;http://c133.org/tmp/libhb-dvd.diff&quot;&gt;this patch&lt;/a&gt; up to fix it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also, I don&apos;t have a video iPod at the moment, or a Sony PSP (and I don&apos;t see myself buying the latter anytime soon, but you know... if one were to fall into my lap, I&apos;d probably use it and enjoy the hell out of it.) Anyway, not owning one of these devices, I&apos;m more interested in HandBrake as a way to make high-quality compressed archives of my DVD movies that I can watch on the HDTV in the living room. There&apos;s a problem, though; HandBrake scales the picture by default as it transcodes it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://c133.org/tmp/enc-pixelratio.diff&quot;&gt;Not anymore&lt;/a&gt;, it doesn&apos;t. Now it has support for (optionally) embedding the anamorphic pixel ratio into the output file, and can preserve the original DVD video frames. Which means, with x264 at least, a reasonable performance increase of about 15%. Not too shabby!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, the only GUIs for HandBrake are on Mac OS X and BeOS. Now, I love BeOS. Haven&apos;t used it in years, though, and I don&apos;t even think it&apos;ll run on my hardware; Haiku still isn&apos;t quite there yet, either, but I&apos;m keeping tabs on it. What I really wanted is a Linux UI for HandBrake.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, I&apos;ve been hacking on one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;http://c133.org/qhandbrake-1.png&quot; alt=&quot;Qt4 HandBrake UI&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned for more on this...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>