<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>almost wrecked my car tonight</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/almost_wrecked_my_car_tonight.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2004 02:20 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I dropped tberman off at the Westford Regency Inn and on the way home, I took exit #35B from the 495. That particular exit is a little bit sharp. I was going about thirty and I probably should have been going about twenty, and my car started to slide as it hydroplaned. Amazingly enough, I managed to control the slide and even though I did pull a *sweet* 180, I didn&apos;t even scratch the car. Nor did I get hurt.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So for all you folks out there rooting for my death, I have cheated you once again. Bitches.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>whoops</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/whoops.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 25 Sep 2004 21:52 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Ran out of disk space on tycho for a minute there.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For those of you who don&apos;t know, tycho is the machine which hosts not only c133.org (and this my web site and email) but also planetKDE.org and Daniel Stone&apos;s fooishbar.org.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So when it runs out of disk space, planet KDE goes down and my email stops arriving which makes me sad.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was getting to be about time to archive the email off again anyway. I&apos;m up to 100M again in my Maildirs. Ugh.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>bitchin&apos; home-made tesla coil</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/bitchin_home_made_tesla_coil.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2004 09:18 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;HDTV service was installed and turned on yesterday. Still feeling a little sick and not so hot, but I&apos;m going in to work today.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The new Smallville season looks &lt;b&gt;good&lt;/b&gt; so far. I love that show. I have to admit, I didn&apos;t really like Lois at first but her personality has already started growing on me. I just wish that Comcast offered the WB in HD up here.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>daddy needs his medicine</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/daddy_needs_his_medicine.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 21 Sep 2004 12:16 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Steph got me sick.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She had a runny nose and a little tiny wussy cough when she came up this weekend but it hit me quite a bit harder last night. This morning doesn&apos;t feel quite so bad - my throat is still a little sore, and my sinuses are a little clogged up, but my nose is mostly not running now. Which is definitely an improvement.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even my tattoo can&apos;t make up for the inherent unsexiness of coughing my brains out.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still evaluating whether or not Cassie will be safe from infection if I go to see her today. Should probably find a doctor... I have health benefits for a reason, right?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>bored bored bored bored bored</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/bored_bored_bored_bored_bored.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2004 19:09 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Nothing&apos;s going on. Everything is just kind of laid-back and I&apos;m cool with that, except that I have nobody to hang around and do nothing with.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Doing nothing alone is weak. Doing nothing with other people around is fun. At least then you can have conversations and good times.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just don&apos;t feel like getting up though. I mean, I&apos;m typing this laying down on my sofa, in my living room... the keyboard is resting with one end on the sofa and the other propped up against my leg, the mouse is on the armrest, and I&apos;m laying down with my head facing out, tilted slightly up so I can see th emonitor. I don&apos;t know if I can get much lazier than this.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Life is good.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>what kind of madman are you?!?!</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/KDE/what_kind_of_madman_are_you.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2004 14:09 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;mattr just asked me on IRC why exactly it is that I want to write YAIMC (Yet Another Instant Messenger Client) and this is my response, for those of you who aren&apos;t really paying attention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;09:55 [mattr] clee: then why don&apos;t you spend time to either suggest improvements or improve the other existing ones?&lt;br /&gt;09:55 [clee] mattr: Because the kinds of &quot;improvements&quot; that I&apos;m going to suggest for kopete and for gaim and for every other client out there will get A) Laughed at or B) Ignored&lt;br /&gt;09:55 [mattr] clee: and you know this how?&lt;br /&gt;09:55 [clee] mattr: Ok, let&apos;s see your reaction to these suggestions.&lt;br /&gt;09:56 [clee] 1) Drop every protocol except OSCAR.&lt;br /&gt;09:56 [clee] 2) Strip out most of the &apos;plugin-based&apos; API for everything.&lt;br /&gt;09:56 [clee] 3) Redesign the UI to not suck.&lt;br /&gt;09:56 [ShawnLaptop] clee: what kind of IM protocols will it support than?&lt;br /&gt;09:56 [clee] ShawnLaptop: ICQ and AIM.&lt;br /&gt;09:56 [clee] Which are the only ones that I give a flying fuck about.&lt;br /&gt;09:56 [ShawnLaptop] MSN, Jabber, Yahoo?&lt;br /&gt;09:56 [clee] Fucke&apos;m.&lt;br /&gt;09:57 [clee] er, Fuck&apos;em.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was a lull while mattr went to go get lunch, and then the discussion started back up again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;10:36 [mattr] clee: you better hope your IM client isn&apos;t any good, because then people will want you to have plugins, and support other protocols. :P&lt;br /&gt;10:36 [clee] mattr: Oh, it won&apos;t be.&lt;br /&gt;10:36 [clee] mattr: As a matter of fact, I&apos;m going to hardcode my username and password into it.&lt;br /&gt;10:37 [clee] mattr: There will be zero preferences, because all behavior will be hardcoded to exactly the way that *I* like it&lt;br /&gt;10:37 [clee] mattr: And if anybody doesn&apos;t like it, they can go fuck themselves and/or fork it themselves&lt;br /&gt;10:37 [mattr] heh&lt;br /&gt;10:38  * mattr notes that he neither laughed nor ignored clee&apos;s suggestions. :P&lt;br /&gt;10:38 [clee] mattr: But you won&apos;t implement them.&lt;br /&gt;10:38 [clee] mattr: And if you did, you&apos;d ruin Kopete.&lt;br /&gt;10:38 [clee] so it&apos;s ok.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To be honest, I may not even release the code to the rest of the world. What with my username and password being hardcoded into it. But we&apos;ll see.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>whoops! dart in your neck</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/whoops_dart_in_your_neck.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2004 02:32 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;My evil plot to subvert GNOME is slowly taking shape. Todd Berman is talking about having me help him with some C# bindings for libgaim. Not only will this rock because I may have a decent API to model my own IM client&apos;s after once the C# bindings are working, but it has the benefit of letting me learn a lot more about C# and Mono.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So many things I need to take care of tech-wise... still have to actually run a power cord to the quad PPro in the closet, have to set up LDAP accounts on it and Kerberos with some sort of filesharing for the home directories and then get the client computers here to work properly with that. Want to set up Ubuntu on one of my machines here since it seems to be pretty cool and I&apos;m all about Debian without the brain damage. Need to figure out whether or not to leave the Radeon 9600 in my desktop or put back in the Radeon 8500 (or the GeForce4MX since the nvidia driver is the only one that actually gives reasonable performance with Composite right now...)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not to mention work stuff. Oy. Not enough hours in the day. And where the hell are my clones, dammit? I&apos;m kinda under-staffed here.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>enough talk. let&apos;s ... kill a human</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/enough_talk_lets_kill_a_human.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2004 02:28 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Can&apos;t figure out why I can&apos;t sleep. Normally I have no problems falling asleep, but the past few days have sucked pretty badly. No idea what the fuck is going on but I&apos;m not digging it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The other thing that&apos;s really screwing with me is that even though it&apos;s taking me forever to get to sleep, my body seems to think that waking up at about 7AM is perfect. My brain disagrees pretty violently. It goes something like this:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;06:59 [body] HEY IT IS TIME TO WAKE UP WAHOO MOVING NOW&lt;br /&gt;06:59 [brain] what the... son of a bitch, CUT THAT SHIT OUT&lt;br /&gt;07:00 [body] hmmm.&lt;br /&gt;07:02 [body] NOPE! MOVING AROUND AND GETTING UP NOW&lt;br /&gt;07:02 [brain] I swear... you will pay for this.&lt;br /&gt;07:28 [brain] holy shit, why am I awake?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ugh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Steph came back up today. Kinda caught me by surprise since I wasn&apos;t even sure if she was going to come up at all. She picked up &lt;b&gt;Super Troopers&lt;/b&gt; which is absolutely hysterical. I got the new Bowling for Soup album, with the song 1985 on it for her at Barnes &amp;amp; Noble. (She loves that song.) Typical whiny punk stuff, but the song is definitely catchy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>the usual kind</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/the_usual_kind.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2004 21:21 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;The ride back from Long Island last night was unbelievable. The fog was incredible - I literally could not see three cars ahead of me at times. Not that there were any cars on the road anyway, but still - the visibility levels hit some pretty scary depths on the 495. And the temperature dropped pretty low as well; not sure if that was a side effect of the speed I was driving at, or both windows being down, or what, but it was pretty crazy.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The weekend in general was just a crazy wild ride. Got to see Kyle again, which is always a good time. I&apos;m proud that he&apos;s my friend. His pimposity has reached awesome new highs, and I have to salute him; we had a blast. Watched the Punisher on DVD as well, which was awesome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not everything went perfectly, of course, but hey. Life goes on.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>and I&apos;ve heard great things, Kevin</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/and_ive_heard_great_things_kevin.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2004 01:22 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Got another new keyboard. The Logitech one that I was happy with before ended up not being nearly as rockalicious as I had initially thought. Programmable keys, yada yada, USB blah blah, shitty. No, &lt;a href=&quot;http://christopher.aillon.org/&quot;&gt;caillon&lt;/a&gt; was cool enough to buy me a &lt;a href=&quot;http://modelm.org/&quot;&gt;Model M keyboard&lt;/a&gt;. CLICKETY FOR LIFE!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And since I have had this one in my hands, I have realized just how much faster and more accurately I type on these keyboards. I missed that feeling. If only someone would make a USB-native Model M... (Oh, and I ordered another one from eBay which was apparently delivered to my apartment&apos;s office building this morning but I wasn&apos;t here.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seriously. These keyboards totally rule.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Incidentally, the one that caillon purchased was in fact not an original Model M but remade by the Keepers of the One True Keyboard, those saints at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pckeyboard.com/&quot;&gt;PC Keyboard&lt;/a&gt;. These guys rule. I have no relation to them save that of the delighted recipient of one of their fine products.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>wonder if it&apos;s legal to sell this stuff to kids</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/wonder_if_its_legal_to_sell_this_stuff_to_kids.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2004 01:12 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Work continues to rock. I was at the office until about half past ten tonight and I didn&apos;t even realize it. Crazy, but in a good way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Talked to Kyle. He&apos;s flying up to Long Island tomorrow. We&apos;re working out the whole schedule for me to go visit him while he&apos;s there - I think I&apos;m driving down on Saturday but we&apos;ll see what happens. Haven&apos;t seen that crazy bastard in months, so there&apos;s no way I can miss this - he doesn&apos;t come up here that often. Have my fingers crossed - hoping that I can score the condo out in Moriches bay for Saturday night and Sunday morning, but I don&apos;t want to count my chickens before they hatch...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cassie continues to surprise me with new levels of ass-kickery. I&apos;m still absolutely shocked that someone as cool as her is remotely interested in me. Not complaining, mind you, but this kind of thing simply doesn&apos;t happen to yours truly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still haven&apos;t gotten tired of macaroni and cheese. Which is a really good thing, I think, since I suspect I&apos;m going to be eating it pretty frequently for the next few days. Until I get paid on Wednesday that is. (Which dovetails nicely with Cassie swinging by. Should remember to clean the apartment before she gets here. It&apos;d be terribly embarassing if she got lost in the mess.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Steph continues to amuse me. I have high hopes that she&apos;ll figure out what it is that she wants someday, but I don&apos;t know when that day will be. The sooner the better. Should be interesting to see how she and Cassie get along... they still haven&apos;t met yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For some reason, the scent of saltwater was &lt;b&gt;really&lt;/b&gt; strong in the air when I was driving home from visiting Cassie at the dorm. This was unexpected, but extremely pleasant. I miss the ocean.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>the black death is coming</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/the_black_death_is_coming.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 09 Sep 2004 00:24 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I have decided that from now on I&apos;m going to use random Sealab quotes (or maybe one-liners from bash.org) as my blog titles.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cassie totally kicks ass. (Those of you who have been reading my blog for a while now may ask yourselves - Cassie? Who is this Cassie? And what happened to Libby?)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;No, my blog has not in fact turned into a soap opera. As cool as that would be, I think that the technologies involved are nowhere near the level that they would need to be for real soap opera goodness. However, my own personal life has been pretty complicated lately, so I&apos;ll lay it out...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Libby was awesome and I hit on her at Hot Topic, where she works - however, despite my initial interpretation of good signals, Libby apparently doesn&apos;t want a boyfriend, and she doesn&apos;t actually seem to want to hang out with me even as friends, so she&apos;s been written off.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cassie on the other hand, completely rules. She hit on me on the Internet, which is a first, and she also lives relatively close. She just moved into the dorm at a college that is about half an hour away, and I went over there today. We watched &lt;i&gt;Underworld&lt;/i&gt;, which was awesome in the same terrible way that &lt;i&gt;Starship Troopers&lt;/i&gt; was. Some of the worst acting I&apos;ve ever seen, coupled with impressive special effects and the most predictable plotlines you could ever imagine, and I&apos;m hooked.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let&apos;s see, what else? Cassie is short. Really really short. Like five foot one short. And she&apos;s really cute. Her hair is brunette (which is ok, as redheads are all batshit insane anyway) and it&apos;s terrifyingly long. She&apos;s eighteen, which is ok, since I&apos;m still only twenty, but she acts a bit more mature than most of the other eighteen year olds that I know, so we&apos;ll see how that works out. She also is a huge video game fanatic, which is ridiculously sweet. And her favorite Final Fantasy was VII, which is a pretty damned good choice for a favorite.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;She also knows every single Sealab quote that I&apos;ve thrown at her. Which for some reason is a huge turn-on to me. She laughs at my jokes, too, and she even completes some of the quotes when I start them.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So, life is interesting, at least. Just when I&apos;ve actually really decided to give up on women, fate throws another one at me. I should really do this whole &quot;giving up on women&quot; thing more often, if this is the result...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>disabled account</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/KDE/disabled_account.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 04 Sep 2004 15:25 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Sashmit, your site appears to have moved to a new host, and cron has sent me a few dozen emails about a 404 on your blog. Drop me an email when it&apos;s back up so I can uncomment your feed again :)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>