<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>this is a test from my tack app</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/KDE/this_is_a_test_from_my_tack_app.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2004 07:52 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;hooray! I have a test app! :D&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>200 gig hard drive</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/200_gig_hard_drive.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2004 01:04 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;So I got a 200G hard drive today. My dad decided to buy it for me as payment for all of the work I&apos;ve been doing trying to get his printer working exactly the way he wants it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Mmmmm. New hardware. I&apos;ve completed the move of my /home over to the new drive, and now it&apos;s just a matter of wiping the 20G drive with my operating systems on it and using the 40G drive that previously held /home as my new OS drive. (I can fit more operating systems in 40G than I can in 20G! WOOOHOOO!)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also, having the laser printer connected to the Mac works seamlessly with KDE over the network. I just pointed a KDE app at the Mac&apos;s IP, and it automatically grokked the print queue and even showed me both printers that have been connected to the Mac - nifty stuff. I love open source software.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(still have to make progress on some sort of a KDE-pyblosxom client. moving that to the top of the TODO, once I&apos;m done screwing with the hard drives.)&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>temet nosce</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/temet_nosce.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Jan 2004 00:53 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I got into a funny conversation with Steph about marriage (of all things) earlier. I have a friend who lives in Minnesota and we were chatting the other day - the gist of the conversation was that since I&apos;m going to Syracuse, and potentially staying for a while, and applying to work at S.U., I would be getting free tuition. I joked that it&apos;d be convenient for her to just marry me and move in with me so she could take advantage of the free tuition (in the event that I do stay in Syracuse and that I&apos;m working at S.U.).&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Steph exploded when I told her about this, revealing much more than I think she intended. &quot;You can&apos;t just marry someone for convenience! That&apos;s completely the wrong reason to get married! What are you, retarded?&quot; Apparently Steph still believes that people should only get married if they&apos;re in love. I think that&apos;s pretty amusing, personally, just because it doesn&apos;t seem to be that common a view among the 20+ crowd that we&apos;re going to be joining this year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Would I actually marry someone for convenience? I don&apos;t know. Would I do it just for sex? Nah. Would I do it for the convenience of a lower insurance premium? Probably not. But would I do it if I knew that it was someone who would put up with me and keep me company so I wouldn&apos;t have to be alone? That&apos;s the one I&apos;m not really too sure about. I hate being alone. I mean, I don&apos;t mind being left alone for a while if I&apos;m busy doing something important but I just don&apos;t enjoy being single.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Part of the problem, I think, is that I&apos;m not nearly as confident as Steph is that I&apos;m going to find that special someone. I mean, I don&apos;t think I&apos;m quite troll-like (well, as long as I shower and shave, that is), but I&apos;m not going to be featured on the cover of GQ anytime soon, and it&apos;s not like I go clubbing or anything. Not that I&apos;d necessarily want to date anybody that I might meet clubbing - that whole idea scares me. But I&apos;m not that attractive and I&apos;m not that social, and most of the women I&apos;m interested in aren&apos;t interested back. The few that I&apos;ve dated that have been interested in me for me have ended up cheating on me (or wanting to and thus ending the relationship) so I don&apos;t really feel quite so self-confident anymore. Am I self-doubting? No, because I think the whole concept of self-doubt involves insecurity and questioning things, while I&apos;m fairly sure of my lesser qualities. I also think that&apos;s one of the reasons I get a kick out of helping people - I feel better about myself when I know that I&apos;m having a positive effect on others. Which, I think, also explains my whole knight-in-shining-armor complex.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Felt kind of weird to realize that I&apos;m the friend Steph calls when she&apos;s got &quot;alone time&quot; while she&apos;s up in Idaho. Yeah, definitely weird.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>