<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>tack release</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/KDE/tack_release.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2004 08:21 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;With the advent of &lt;a href=&quot;http://planetkde.org/&quot;&gt;planet KDE&lt;/a&gt;, we need a decent blog posting utility for KDE. This isn&apos;t it, but it might become that utility if enough people send patches to me (or hey, you can always fork it!)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ladies and gentlemen, without further ado, I present to you:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://c133.org/files/tack-0.0.tar.bz2&quot;&gt;Tack 0.0&lt;/a&gt;, the most minimalist and feature-starved blog posting utility KDE has ever seen. It needs loving, lots of it, and as I&apos;m going to be on an airplane later on today I can&apos;t give it the loving it so deserves.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So download it, marvel at its simplicity and lack of functionality, and then hack on it and send me patches so that it stops sucking so much.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That is all.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>planet KDE</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/KDE/planet_kde.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 06 Jun 2004 06:08 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I was discussing how addictive &lt;a href=&quot;http://planet.gnome.org/&quot;&gt;Planet GNOME&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&quot;http://planet.debian.net/&quot;&gt;Planet Debian&lt;/a&gt; are on #kde-devel with a few KDE developers and we lamented the lack of a Planet KDE. However, unlike them, I actually decided to get up and do something about it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Behold! &lt;a href=&quot;http://planetkde.org/&quot;&gt;Planet KDE&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yes. It&apos;s ugly. It&apos;s also fairly empty. Until &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.kdedevelopers.org/blog/geiseri&quot;&gt;Ian&lt;/a&gt; fixes up kdedevelopers.org (see how &lt;a href=&quot;http://planetkde.org/broken.html&quot;&gt;messed up&lt;/a&gt; the feeds are?) so that it includes &amp;lt;pubDate&amp;gt; tags so that the blog entries get sorted correctly, we&apos;re pretty lonely over here.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The good news is, if you&apos;re a KDE developer with a blog on your own site, &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:clee@kde.org&quot;&gt;mail me&lt;/a&gt; the URL of your properly-formed RSS feed, tell me what you do in KDE, and I&apos;ll add you to the blogroll as soon as possible.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>