<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>another day, another server</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/another_day_another_server.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2004 05:56 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;The machine which was previously hosting c133.org (my domain) was compromised recently. So I set about finding new hosting, and I did thanks to Warren Togami (a coworker of mine at Red Hat) so you are now seeing c133.org on a brand-new box.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One interesting side effect of this is that my weblog is now statically generated instead of dynamically so. I haven&apos;t really changed the layout or anything, or even the design, but the filesystem paths have been played with a bit and the configuration has been gently tweaked. So now my blog should be even faster.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oh, and &lt;a href=&quot;http://planetKDE.org/&quot;&gt;planet KDE&lt;/a&gt; has a new home as well. Thanks to Stephen Depooter, it&apos;s now on a separate machine from c133.org and very unscientific cursory testing shows to me that it&apos;s even more well-connected than it was before. So, despite the fact that the breakin shut down the sites, I think that they&apos;re both better off now. And my mail seems to have mostly caught up with itself. Which is good.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;now that I&apos;ve been forced to get off my ass and actually look over the files on the site, I&apos;ve done a little tiny bit of maintenance and cleaned up a few things that were previously still around. I may even get around to doing the aforementioned redesign at some point! But I don&apos;t want to make any promises, so I won&apos;t.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>