<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>dear diary</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/dear_diary.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 19 Mar 2006 00:40 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;JACKPOT.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My girlfriend knows the cheat codes to the GTA games, by heart.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sorry, just had to brag about that.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>rumors and lies</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/rumors_and_lies.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2006 20:01 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;It&apos;s been a while since I last blogged; I know, I suck. Deal with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was supposed to be in Norway as of two months ago, but as it turns out, the Norwegian government apparently hates me. My work visa has yet to be approved, so I&apos;m currently in California working at Trolltech&apos;s office in Palo Alto on a short-term contract.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&quot;But, Chris - how did you end up in California? I thought you were in Boston!&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yes, yes, I was. I was in Boston until I ran out of sofas to crash on. Then I took my car and talked a crazy friend of mine (the &lt;a href=&quot;http://naim.n.ml.org/&quot;&gt;author of naim&lt;/a&gt; to be precise) into doing a cross-country road trip with me. We made the trip from Boston to Phoenix in about forty-two hours, give or take.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I spent a few weeks in Chandler, leeching off of my parents, and generally trying to figure out my next move. I had a lot of fun while I was there - my friend Josh left for the Navy right before I left to come out here to CA, so I was there for his sendoff party, and that was pretty great.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oh, and I have a girlfriend now - scarily enough, she&apos;s not completely insane or otherwise mentally handicapped, yet she still likes me. So, to all my secret admirers out there: You should&apos;ve moved faster! Now I&apos;m taken, and it&apos;s too late.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Saturday can&apos;t get here fast enough.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>metropolitan moving sucks</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/metropolitan_moving_sucks.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2006 20:00 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;My friend Jeannette had a terrible time with &lt;a href=&quot;http://butterflyintraining.blogspot.com/2006/03/metropolitan-moving-is-one-of-worst.html&quot;&gt;Metropolitan Moving&lt;/a&gt;. If you&apos;re going to be moving anytime soon, I&apos;d suggest avoiding them.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>