<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>And now for something completely the same.</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/And_now_for_something_completely_the_same.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jan 2004 23:44 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;So I just went through a fairly messy breakup with Mickey, who I&apos;d been with for well over a year and a half. It turns out that she slept with her (ex?)-best-friend Andrew back in October, and I found out about it just in time for Christmas. Great Christmas present.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ugh. I feel like an ass. I guess it&apos;s a good thing that it happened at this point instead of later on, down the road, after more wasted time and such. Still, it sucks. I hate being alone. I had almost conquered my adequacy issues for a while there, too. Not to mention my problems with trusting people.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And then today I find out another great bit of news: Mickey&apos;s already got a new boyfriend. Way to go. I want her to be happy. I want to be happy too though, and this doesn&apos;t help me towards that goal at all. Two days ago she was swearing up and down that she didn&apos;t want to date anyone ever again and that she&apos;d wait forever for me to forgive her and then this turns up. Good times. I have no idea how long it&apos;ll take me to get over her. Steff and I only dated for three or four months, but it took me a year and a half before I was ready for another relationship; I&apos;m afraid of how long it might take before I&apos;m actually ready for the next one, if there&apos;ll even be a next one.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;(For those among you who don&apos;t know - Steff was my first serious girlfriend and Steph is her ex-best-friend. Steff and I don&apos;t talk. Steff and Steph don&apos;t talk. Steph and I talk all the time, and we&apos;re pretty good friends.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Oh well. The road trip to Colorado was awesome. Hands-down the most fun I&apos;ve had in years. Steph is awesome. And I forgot just how well Kyle and I get along. He&apos;s a rarity, I think - a truly great friend, not just someone fun to hang out with but someone that I know would take a bullet for me and someone I&apos;d take do the same for without a second thought. You don&apos;t stumble across a friendship like that too often. Steph is completely head over heels for him, of course; and his girlfriend Krystal is also amazing. She&apos;s really cute, and she seems like a great match for him. I&apos;m glad for him - they make a good couple. Steph isn&apos;t so glad, as she&apos;s so into him, but she&apos;ll have to figure out some way of dealing with it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Speaking of Steph, it turns out that her grandmother died a day or two after we got back from CO. Not cool. It kind of puts a shitty pall over the memory of the trip because we were sitting there having a grand ol&apos; time while her grandma was dying. Another reason for me to feel like an ass.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I love my keyboard. Logitech stuff hasn&apos;t impressed me this much in the past, but now I&apos;m thinking that my next keyboard purchase will probably also be a Logitech as well. I still like the Microsoft optical mice though.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;KDE stuff is always interesting. I got free access to the Lindows ISOs today by virtue of my being a KDE developer as well as eV member. I sent an email to Michael Robertson (CEO of Lindows and generally very cool guy) mentioning that I&apos;d be more than happy to work with Lindows to develop a distinctive and professional GUI widget style for them but I haven&apos;t heard anything back yet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>