<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>it&apos;s time for the &quot;I Hate Marco Show!&quot;</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/i_hate_marco_show.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2006 05:26 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;So it&apos;s been playing for a few weeks now, and I just felt that it needed to be shared with everyone who reads this blog:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.imdb.com/title/tt0773262/&quot;&gt;Dexter&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don&apos;t really know exactly how to put it into words, but there is something that is sick, and twisted, and oh-so-right about this show that makes me laugh. The writing, as &lt;a href=&quot;http://aseigo.blogspot.com/2006/11/kde-on-tv.html&quot;&gt;aseigo noted&lt;/a&gt; is amazing, and the plot throughout Season One so far has been gripping.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you have a weak stomach, you might not like it. It&apos;s definitely not a show for the young ones, either - strong language, some nudity, lots of very graphic scenes. The really amusing thing to me, at least, is that the &lt;b&gt;really&lt;/b&gt; graphic scenes are not even of violent acts; whoever is handling the visuals for the show is an absolute genius. Simple acts like tying shoes and pulling on a T-shirt somehow take on a much more sinister undertone.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I &lt;b&gt;highly&lt;/b&gt; recommend checking this show out. It is, by far, my favorite new show this season, so far even moreso than Heroes. Heroes keeps leading me along and throwing me a bone every now and then, but Dexter has been delivering since Episode One and I haven&apos;t been disappointed yet.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>