<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>qotd</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/qotd_sep_24_2007.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 24 Sep 2007 20:03 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;b&gt;davej&lt;/b&gt;&amp;gt; so mountain dew have made a huge fuck up.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;b&gt;davej&lt;/b&gt;&amp;gt; they marketed this drink to me as &apos;game fuel&apos;.   but it tastes distinctly like &apos;ass fuel&apos;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>announcing MobilePushr</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/announcing_mobilepushr.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 21 Sep 2007 04:18 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;When I first heard that the iPhone had a camera built-in, as well as WiFi, those two features triggered the following thought:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;blockquote&gt;It would be really hot if you could upload the pictures from the camera directly to Flickr.&lt;/blockquote&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I got my iPhone, I figured out a workflow that I could use to post pictures from the phone to my Flickr account, but it &lt;strike&gt;totally sucked balls&lt;/strike&gt; was less than optimal. For each picture I wanted to upload, I had to open the picture in the Photos app and email it to a special address that Flickr had associated with my account.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Negatives of this approach? Impossible to use for more than a couple of images at a time, primarily, but also, annoyingly, the Mail app on the iPhone scales and recompresses the JPEG images before sending - and it strips them of their EXIF data, too.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I was mildly displeased, but there was a way I could get it to work, kinda.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then the iPhone got cracked wide open. People started figuring out how to write third-party apps and get them installed on their iPhones, and - to be honest - the UI for it, via Installer.app, is - even though it&apos;s not from Apple - better than anything I&apos;ve seen on any other mobile phone, ever.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Friday before last (September 7th), I decided it was time to take matters into my own hands. Finally learn Objective C. Start writing my dedicated &quot;Push all of the images in my Camera Roll to Flickr, right now dammit&quot; application. And I got a pretty good start! Got the toolchain to build working iPhone apps, and that only took a few hours. Started reading through Flickr&apos;s API documentation. Started implementing some functions that didn&apos;t require authorization to call - learning how to use Flickr&apos;s REST API, basically. Once the first couple of unauthenticated calls worked and did what I expected, I knew it would only be a matter of time before I had my app working.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And then someone pointed me to &lt;a href=&quot;http://http://code.google.com/p/iflickr/&quot;&gt;iFlickr&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My first thought was &quot;Dammit, somebody beat me to it.&quot; And I was a little depressed for a bit.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I downloaded it and tried to get it working. No offense to the iFlickr devs, but they clearly didn&apos;t put a lot of thought into the user experience (or if they did, I posit that their ideas about &quot;good user experience&quot; work completely differently from mine). I didn&apos;t end up getting it to work, but it&apos;s open-source, right?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Naturally, my next thought: &quot;Well, I&apos;ve been working on mine, and this doesn&apos;t really do what I wanted. But... maybe I can steal some of their code at least!&quot;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And then I looked at the code.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My eyes still burn a little bit from that. That ... that was not a good idea. I&apos;ve had much better ideas in the past.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I worked on this for the next few nights, realized that I could completely avoid the messy minitoken crap by using the &quot;Desktop app&quot; authentication mode from Flickr, deleted all of my code that dealt with mini-tokens, and the other night, I finally got it to actually upload pictures to my Flickr account. (My friend &lt;a href=&quot;http://cliffhacks.blogspot.com/&quot;&gt;Cliff&lt;/a&gt;&apos;s help was so valuable as to be incalculable.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&apos;ll post more technical details later, but the important thing is: &lt;a href=&quot;http://mobilepushr.jottit.com/&quot;&gt;MobilePushr&lt;/a&gt; is out. The UI is going to get a lot of love in the next few days, because the current one doesn&apos;t provide nearly enough feedback, but as of right now, MobilePushr lets me do something that I&apos;ve wanted for almost three months. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I can push my JPEGs directly from my iPhone to my Flickr account with the push of a single, giant red button. (And so can you! If you go download it and install it on your iPhone, that is. Assuming you have an iPhone.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also, of course, MobilePushr is Open Source / Free Software, released under the GPLv2. If you use git, you can look at my code by cloning git://mg8.org/MobilePushr and poking around.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The really awesome thing about all of this is that, through Flickr, I can see how many people have given my app permission to link to their account, and in the first twelve hours alone over a thousand people have activated support for MobilePushr on their Flickr accounts.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I don&apos;t even have words to describe how awesome that makes me feel.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>qotd</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/qotd_sep_20_2007.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 20 Sep 2007 18:09 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;b&gt;ajax&lt;/b&gt;&amp;gt; it&apos;s like kicking a puppy&lt;br /&gt;&amp;lt;&lt;b&gt;ajax&lt;/b&gt;&amp;gt; ... in that&apos;s it&apos;s really fun&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>qotd</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/qotd_jun12_2007.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jun 2007 13:46 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;ajax&amp;gt; i pick good days to go to olpc office&lt;br /&gt;&amp;lt;ajax&amp;gt; free ice cream in the lobby&lt;br /&gt;&amp;lt;keithp&amp;gt; ajax: winning&lt;br /&gt;&amp;lt;keithp&amp;gt; ajax: where is it from?&lt;br /&gt;&amp;lt;ajax&amp;gt; buckets?&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>did you know?</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/did_you_know.html</link>
    <pubDate>Mon, 11 Jun 2007 19:52 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.codemonkey.org.uk/projects/x86info/&quot;&gt;x86info&lt;/a&gt; is awesome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Unfortunately, &lt;a href=&quot;http://kernelslacker.livejournal.com/80434.html&quot;&gt;SourceForge is not so awesome&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>qotd</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/qotd_may15_2007.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 15 May 2007 16:42 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;mjg59&amp;gt; daniels: You&apos;d better be getting dolla dolla for this&lt;br /&gt;&amp;lt;daniels&amp;gt; mjg59: well, euro euro, but yeah&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>qotd</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/qotd_apr26_2007.html</link>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Apr 2007 20:04 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;&amp;lt;ajax&amp;gt; yum, well.  let&apos;s not mention yum.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;lt;clee&amp;gt; ajax: I thought you were making yum not suck.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;lt;ajax&amp;gt; clee: i realized life was short and i wanted to work on something that stands the remotest chance in hell of getting me laid&lt;br /&gt;&amp;lt;clee&amp;gt; ajax: I thought you already got guaranteed sex.&lt;br /&gt;&amp;lt;ajax&amp;gt; HEY I MADE THE UPDATER FASTER: &quot;eew, go away&quot;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;lt;davej&amp;gt; &quot;Hey baby, want to see multiple graphic cards working at once?  huh?&quot;&lt;br /&gt;&amp;lt;ajax&amp;gt; DUDE CHECK OUT THIS GADGET IT&apos;S WAY CUTE AND HAS WOBBLY WINDOWS: &quot;ooh, i spreads for you&quot;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>they&apos;re gonna hunt me? for sport?</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/for_sport.html</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 Jan 2007 06:44 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Can&apos;t really think of anything funny or clever to say about this; I had surgery for my hernia today, and it went well, I suppose. I survived, and now I have a surprisingly large incision which has been covered in superglue. It&apos;s going to form a bad-ass scar.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My surgeon prescribed vicodin and ibuprofen. I&apos;m not entirely sure that either of those is helping me at all.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was told before I went under the knife that the vicodin they were giving me was basically diazepam, which made me think of Metal Gear Solid, and I was happy. Visions of long, drawn-out boss fights with Sniper Wolf danced through my head. Unfortunately, it turns out that the nurse lied to me, and vicodin is not in fact diazepam.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Incidentally, I had my prescriptions filled at Target, because of their totally sweet ClearRx bottles. If you haven&apos;t heard of them, you should &lt;a href=&quot;http://nymag.com/nymetro/health/features/11700/&quot;&gt;check out the story&lt;/a&gt; about why they&apos;re awesome.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anyway. I&apos;m alive, and that&apos;s something.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>qotd</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/qotd_jan3_2007.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 03 Jan 2007 19:10 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;lt;clee&amp;gt;&lt;/b&gt; man, git hates me.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;lt;daniels&amp;gt;&lt;/b&gt; git does not love&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;lt;daniels&amp;gt;&lt;/b&gt; occasionally it roughly pleasures&lt;br /&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;lt;daniels&amp;gt;&lt;/b&gt; but there&apos;s no tender embrace, and definitely no breakfast the next morning&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>