<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>and I&apos;ve heard great things, Kevin</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/and_ive_heard_great_things_kevin.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2004 01:22 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Got another new keyboard. The Logitech one that I was happy with before ended up not being nearly as rockalicious as I had initially thought. Programmable keys, yada yada, USB blah blah, shitty. No, &lt;a href=&quot;http://christopher.aillon.org/&quot;&gt;caillon&lt;/a&gt; was cool enough to buy me a &lt;a href=&quot;http://modelm.org/&quot;&gt;Model M keyboard&lt;/a&gt;. CLICKETY FOR LIFE!&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And since I have had this one in my hands, I have realized just how much faster and more accurately I type on these keyboards. I missed that feeling. If only someone would make a USB-native Model M... (Oh, and I ordered another one from eBay which was apparently delivered to my apartment&apos;s office building this morning but I wasn&apos;t here.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Seriously. These keyboards totally rule.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Incidentally, the one that caillon purchased was in fact not an original Model M but remade by the Keepers of the One True Keyboard, those saints at &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.pckeyboard.com/&quot;&gt;PC Keyboard&lt;/a&gt;. These guys rule. I have no relation to them save that of the delighted recipient of one of their fine products.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>wonder if it&apos;s legal to sell this stuff to kids</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/wonder_if_its_legal_to_sell_this_stuff_to_kids.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2004 01:12 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Work continues to rock. I was at the office until about half past ten tonight and I didn&apos;t even realize it. Crazy, but in a good way.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Talked to Kyle. He&apos;s flying up to Long Island tomorrow. We&apos;re working out the whole schedule for me to go visit him while he&apos;s there - I think I&apos;m driving down on Saturday but we&apos;ll see what happens. Haven&apos;t seen that crazy bastard in months, so there&apos;s no way I can miss this - he doesn&apos;t come up here that often. Have my fingers crossed - hoping that I can score the condo out in Moriches bay for Saturday night and Sunday morning, but I don&apos;t want to count my chickens before they hatch...&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cassie continues to surprise me with new levels of ass-kickery. I&apos;m still absolutely shocked that someone as cool as her is remotely interested in me. Not complaining, mind you, but this kind of thing simply doesn&apos;t happen to yours truly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still haven&apos;t gotten tired of macaroni and cheese. Which is a really good thing, I think, since I suspect I&apos;m going to be eating it pretty frequently for the next few days. Until I get paid on Wednesday that is. (Which dovetails nicely with Cassie swinging by. Should remember to clean the apartment before she gets here. It&apos;d be terribly embarassing if she got lost in the mess.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Steph continues to amuse me. I have high hopes that she&apos;ll figure out what it is that she wants someday, but I don&apos;t know when that day will be. The sooner the better. Should be interesting to see how she and Cassie get along... they still haven&apos;t met yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For some reason, the scent of saltwater was &lt;b&gt;really&lt;/b&gt; strong in the air when I was driving home from visiting Cassie at the dorm. This was unexpected, but extremely pleasant. I miss the ocean.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>