<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>what kind of madman are you?!?!</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/KDE/what_kind_of_madman_are_you.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2004 14:09 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;mattr just asked me on IRC why exactly it is that I want to write YAIMC (Yet Another Instant Messenger Client) and this is my response, for those of you who aren&apos;t really paying attention.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;09:55 [mattr] clee: then why don&apos;t you spend time to either suggest improvements or improve the other existing ones?&lt;br /&gt;09:55 [clee] mattr: Because the kinds of &quot;improvements&quot; that I&apos;m going to suggest for kopete and for gaim and for every other client out there will get A) Laughed at or B) Ignored&lt;br /&gt;09:55 [mattr] clee: and you know this how?&lt;br /&gt;09:55 [clee] mattr: Ok, let&apos;s see your reaction to these suggestions.&lt;br /&gt;09:56 [clee] 1) Drop every protocol except OSCAR.&lt;br /&gt;09:56 [clee] 2) Strip out most of the &apos;plugin-based&apos; API for everything.&lt;br /&gt;09:56 [clee] 3) Redesign the UI to not suck.&lt;br /&gt;09:56 [ShawnLaptop] clee: what kind of IM protocols will it support than?&lt;br /&gt;09:56 [clee] ShawnLaptop: ICQ and AIM.&lt;br /&gt;09:56 [clee] Which are the only ones that I give a flying fuck about.&lt;br /&gt;09:56 [ShawnLaptop] MSN, Jabber, Yahoo?&lt;br /&gt;09:56 [clee] Fucke&apos;m.&lt;br /&gt;09:57 [clee] er, Fuck&apos;em.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was a lull while mattr went to go get lunch, and then the discussion started back up again.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;10:36 [mattr] clee: you better hope your IM client isn&apos;t any good, because then people will want you to have plugins, and support other protocols. :P&lt;br /&gt;10:36 [clee] mattr: Oh, it won&apos;t be.&lt;br /&gt;10:36 [clee] mattr: As a matter of fact, I&apos;m going to hardcode my username and password into it.&lt;br /&gt;10:37 [clee] mattr: There will be zero preferences, because all behavior will be hardcoded to exactly the way that *I* like it&lt;br /&gt;10:37 [clee] mattr: And if anybody doesn&apos;t like it, they can go fuck themselves and/or fork it themselves&lt;br /&gt;10:37 [mattr] heh&lt;br /&gt;10:38  * mattr notes that he neither laughed nor ignored clee&apos;s suggestions. :P&lt;br /&gt;10:38 [clee] mattr: But you won&apos;t implement them.&lt;br /&gt;10:38 [clee] mattr: And if you did, you&apos;d ruin Kopete.&lt;br /&gt;10:38 [clee] so it&apos;s ok.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;To be honest, I may not even release the code to the rest of the world. What with my username and password being hardcoded into it. But we&apos;ll see.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>whoops! dart in your neck</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/whoops_dart_in_your_neck.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2004 02:32 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;My evil plot to subvert GNOME is slowly taking shape. Todd Berman is talking about having me help him with some C# bindings for libgaim. Not only will this rock because I may have a decent API to model my own IM client&apos;s after once the C# bindings are working, but it has the benefit of letting me learn a lot more about C# and Mono.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So many things I need to take care of tech-wise... still have to actually run a power cord to the quad PPro in the closet, have to set up LDAP accounts on it and Kerberos with some sort of filesharing for the home directories and then get the client computers here to work properly with that. Want to set up Ubuntu on one of my machines here since it seems to be pretty cool and I&apos;m all about Debian without the brain damage. Need to figure out whether or not to leave the Radeon 9600 in my desktop or put back in the Radeon 8500 (or the GeForce4MX since the nvidia driver is the only one that actually gives reasonable performance with Composite right now...)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not to mention work stuff. Oy. Not enough hours in the day. And where the hell are my clones, dammit? I&apos;m kinda under-staffed here.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>enough talk. let&apos;s ... kill a human</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/enough_talk_lets_kill_a_human.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2004 02:28 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Can&apos;t figure out why I can&apos;t sleep. Normally I have no problems falling asleep, but the past few days have sucked pretty badly. No idea what the fuck is going on but I&apos;m not digging it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The other thing that&apos;s really screwing with me is that even though it&apos;s taking me forever to get to sleep, my body seems to think that waking up at about 7AM is perfect. My brain disagrees pretty violently. It goes something like this:&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;06:59 [body] HEY IT IS TIME TO WAKE UP WAHOO MOVING NOW&lt;br /&gt;06:59 [brain] what the... son of a bitch, CUT THAT SHIT OUT&lt;br /&gt;07:00 [body] hmmm.&lt;br /&gt;07:02 [body] NOPE! MOVING AROUND AND GETTING UP NOW&lt;br /&gt;07:02 [brain] I swear... you will pay for this.&lt;br /&gt;07:28 [brain] holy shit, why am I awake?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ugh.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Steph came back up today. Kinda caught me by surprise since I wasn&apos;t even sure if she was going to come up at all. She picked up &lt;b&gt;Super Troopers&lt;/b&gt; which is absolutely hysterical. I got the new Bowling for Soup album, with the song 1985 on it for her at Barnes &amp;amp; Noble. (She loves that song.) Typical whiny punk stuff, but the song is definitely catchy.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>