<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>how disturbing</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/how_disturbing.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2006 03:52 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;[savanah] I&apos;m going to snowball you one of these days, just to show you the difference between sperm and orange pulp&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>tacos are not worth endangering the mission</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/endangering_the_mission.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2006 03:43 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Took a road trip to Arizona this past weekend. It&apos;s a pretty hefty drive from Palo Alto to Phoenix and back; roughly ten or eleven hours each way. I got to spend time with Savanah, though, so as far as I&apos;m concerned it was worth it. Her brother kicked my ass at Halo 2, but that isn&apos;t very surprising since I suck at Halo and its ilk.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I decided that I&apos;m not going to Norway. As much as I would have loved to go, I&apos;m pretty sure it wouldn&apos;t really work out at this point.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I informed Trolltech of my decision last week and when I showed up at work on Monday, I was in turn informed that since I&apos;m not going to Norway, there&apos;s not really any reason for me to stick around in the Palo Alto office; end result, I no longer work for Trolltech.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is kind of cool, actually; it gives me a couple of weeks of free time with money to relax, and as tired as I still am from the road trip, I think I might go back to Arizona again. I might even tell some other people that I&apos;m there this time. I have to be back in time to move into my new apartment though. Since I don&apos;t work at Trolltech, I also don&apos;t get to live in the Trolltech-sponsored housing; I&apos;m crashing at my friend Cliff&apos;s place currently, and I don&apos;t move into my own place until next week.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At least I can&apos;t complain that my life is boring.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>qotd</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/qotd_04012006.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2006 20:48 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;[ajax] zrusin has already threatened me with violence if gobject is ever attached to X&lt;br /&gt;[ajax] and i can&apos;t afford that.  i&apos;m too pretty, and he fights dirty.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>