<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>alvis will smoke those bitches</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/personal/alvis_will_smoke_those_bitches.html</link>
    <pubDate>Wed, 27 Dec 2006 09:09 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;Christmas is always an interesting time of year.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three years ago I had the single worst Christmas ever. The ones since then haven&apos;t been so hot either, until now. This year&apos;s Christmas is officially the best one I&apos;ve ever had.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The reason?&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have finally gotten rid of a car that I hated and I now am the proud owner of a brand-new 2007 Toyota Corolla. It&apos;s got a five-speed manual transmission, and it&apos;s totally freakin&apos; sweet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I&apos;m really excited about getting more than twenty miles per gallon on road trips. I&apos;m hella stoked about having a manual transmission again. But most of all, I&apos;m just happy to finally move past the stage of my life where I was constantly pissed at myself for being so stupid as to get stuck with the previous car.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Anyway. I&apos;m back in Arizona for the holidays, and things are pretty fucking great right now. For the first time in a long time, I&apos;m looking forward to the road trip back home in my car.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;On a slightly-less-awesome newsfront... I get to have surgery next month.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Some of you may know that when I was a teenager, I had a hernia. It wasn&apos;t really anything terribly awful, just a typical hernia; they operated on me when I was nineteen and fixed it up, and everything was great until a couple of months ago. I noticed some similar symptoms to my original hernia, and I finally got off my ass and went to the doctor a few weeks ago. She confirmed it - I am officially on my second hernia. I&apos;m not even twenty-five yet.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, having a car with a real transmission has made me so happy that I&apos;m not even really that upset about the prospect of being cut open and having somebody mess around with my internal organs. It&apos;s going to suck, sure. But I made it through it last time; I&apos;ve got a feeling that I&apos;ll be able to survive this time.&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  <item>
    <title>qotd</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/random/qotd_dec8_2006.html</link>
    <pubDate>Sat, 09 Dec 2006 02:20 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;&amp;lt;ajax&amp;gt;&lt;/b&gt; and if i&apos;m marking up every sdk header _anyway_, i want to make a pass over them eliminating all the cases where we do struct foo { a, b, #ifdef I_KICK_PUPPIES, c, #endif, d, e, f }&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>