<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!-- RSS generated by pyblosxom-1.0.0 -->

<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Lee</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/</link>
    <description>all clee, all the time</description>
    <webMaster>clee@kde.org</webMaster>
    <managingEditor>clee@kde.org</managingEditor>
    <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>implementing ideas</title>
    <link>http://c133.org/blog/tech/implementing_ideas.html</link>
    <pubDate>Fri, 27 Oct 2006 07:02 -1000</pubDate>
    <description>&lt;p&gt;I like getting around to implementing the various ideas that I bounce back and forth inside my skull.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;One of those ideas that I had for a long time was to solder a PS/2-&amp;gt;USB converter directly into an IBM Model M keyboard, along with a USB plug so that I could just swap out USB cables to plug the keyboard into the computer.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://www.flickr.com/photos/12031124@N00/sets/72157594346862373/&quot;&gt;I have finally done that&lt;/a&gt;, after some &lt;a href=&quot;http://zevv.nl/experiments/ibm-usb/&quot;&gt;inspiration from zevv&lt;/a&gt;, a few choice purchases at Fry&apos;s Electronics, and a few borrowed parts from my friend Cliff.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have to say, this kicks way more ass than even I had hoped. (ajax, eat your heart out.)&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Still on the list:&lt;br /&gt;&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;finish the Qt4 frontend for HandBrake&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;write my own email client that doesn&apos;t suck balls&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;write my own AIM client that doesn&apos;t suck balls&lt;/li&gt;&lt;li&gt;hack up some apps for Qtopia/Opie/whatever for my shiny new iPaq 3670&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I know there&apos;s more than that, but those are the ones that are currently taking up the most brainspace, so I&apos;m going to have to get to them sometime.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Due to United Airlines sucking balls, &lt;a href=&quot;http://airlied.livejournal.com/&quot;&gt;Dave Airlie&lt;/a&gt; crashed at my place last night after they called back and cancelled his flight from SFO to Sydney. I&apos;ve said this before, although maybe not on this blog, but United are a bunch of cockbags. They have fucked up at least one leg of every single trip of mine that they&apos;ve ever been involved in. In any case, I know far too many foreigners named Dave.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also, I&apos;ve been growing &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.flickr.com/photos/12031124@N00/280500553/&quot;&gt;this&lt;/a&gt; out for the first time ever. Looks like I&apos;m going to have to update my various avatars...&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
  </item>
  </channel>
</rss>